<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><?xml-stylesheet href="style.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>HKSAR Government Press Releases</title>
		<link>http://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/today.htm</link>
		<image>
			<url>http://www.info.gov.hk/gia/rss/rss_logo_en.gif</url>
			<title>HKSAR Government Press Releases</title>
			<link>http://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/today.htm</link>
		</image>
		<description>HKSAR Government - Press Releases</description>
		<language>en-UK</language>
		<copyright>Copyright, HKSAR Government</copyright>
		<webMaster>irc@isd.gov.hk</webMaster>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 11:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Unauthorised websites, phishing emails and phishing instant messages related to Citibank (Hong Kong) Limited]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700519.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700519.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:58:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) wishes to alert members of the public to a press release issued by Citibank&nbsp;(Hong Kong)&nbsp;Limited relating to unauthorised websites, phishing emails and phishing instant messages, which has been reported to the HKMA. A hyperlink to the press release is available on the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.hkma.gov.hk/eng/smart-consumers/beware-of-fraudsters/#fraudulent-bank-websites-phishing-emails-and-similar-scams" target="_blank">HKMA website</a>.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The HKMA wishes to remind the public that banks will not send SMS or e-mails with embedded hyperlinks which direct them to the banks&#39; websites to carry out transactions. They will not ask customers for sensitive personal information, such as login passwords or one-time password, by phone, email or SMS (including via embedded hyperlinks).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anyone who has provided his or her personal information, or who has conducted any financial transactions, through or in response to the websites, emails or instant messages concerned, should contact the bank using the contact information provided in the press release, and report the matter to the Police by contacting the Cyber Security and Technology Crime Bureau of the Hong Kong Police Force at 2860 5012.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Public hospitals daily update on COVID-19 cases]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700446.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700446.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hospital Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; As at 9am today (November 17), no COVID-19 confirmed patient was discharged from hospital in the last 24 hours. So far, a total of 12 099 patients with confirmed or probable infection have been discharged.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; A total of 41 confirmed patients are currently hospitalised in the North Lantau Hospital Hong Kong Infection Control Centre and the Hospital Authority (HA) Infectious Disease Centre, and all of them are in stable condition.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The HA will maintain close contact with the Centre for Health Protection to monitor the latest developments and to inform the public and healthcare workers on the latest information in a timely manner.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Tender results of one-year HONIA-indexed Floating Rate Notes under Institutional Bond Issuance Programme]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700419.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700419.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority:<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA), as representative of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region Government (HKSAR Government), announced that a tender of one-year HONIA-indexed Floating Rate Notes (issue number 01GH2211) under the Institutional Bond Issuance Programme was held today (November 17).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A total of HK$1.0 billion one-year HONIA-indexed Floating Rate Notes were allocated today. A total of HK$6.417 billion tender applications were received. The bid-to-cover ratio, i.e. the ratio of notes applied for to notes issued, is 6.42. The highest spread accepted is 0.05 per cent.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
HKSAR Government Institutional Bond Issuance Programme Government Bond tender results<br />
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tender results of one-year HONIA-indexed Floating Rate Notes under the Institutional Bond Issuance Programme:<br />
&nbsp;
<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Tender Date</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Issue Number</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">01GH2211</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Stock Code</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">4247 (HKGB FRN 2211)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Issue and Settlement Date</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">November 18, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Tenor</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">1-year</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Maturity Date</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">November 18, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Amount Applied</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">HK$6.417 billion</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Amount Allotted</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">HK$1.0 billion</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Bid-to-Cover Ratio*</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">6.42</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Highest Spread Accepted</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">0.05 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Average Spread Accepted</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">0.03 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Pro-rata Ratio</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">About 68 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:20px; width:231px">Average Tender Spread</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="height:20px; width:308px">0.13 per cent</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;<br />
* Calculated as the amount of notes applied for over the amount of notes issued.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Effective Exchange Rate Index]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700203.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700203.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The effective exchange rate index for the Hong Kong dollar on Wednesday, November 17, 2021 is 101.4 (up 0.3 against yesterday&#39;s index).]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Customs seizes suspected scheduled red sandalwood (with photo)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700353.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700353.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hong Kong Customs seized about 1 930 kilograms of suspected scheduled red sandalwood, with an estimated market value of about $9.63 million, at Hong Kong International Airport from November 8 to yesterday (November 16).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Through risk assessment, Customs officers on November 8 and 10 inspected two air consignments, declared to be carrying ceramic flower pots, arriving in Hong Kong from India. Upon inspection, Customs officers found two batches of suspected scheduled red sandalwood inside 10 carton boxes.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Also, Customs officers yesterday inspected an air consignment, declared to be carrying guitar parts, arriving in Hong Kong from Dubai. Upon inspection, Customs officers found another batch of suspected scheduled red sandalwood inside two large wooden boxes.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The three cases were handed over to the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department for follow-up investigation.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Under the Protection of Endangered Species of Animals and Plants Ordinance, any person found guilty of importing or exporting an endangered species without a licence is liable to a maximum fine of $10 million and imprisonment for 10 years.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Members of the public may report any suspected smuggling activities to Customs&#39; 24-hour hotline 2545 6182 or its dedicated crime-reporting email account (<a href="mailto:crimereport@customs.gov.hk">crimereport@customs.gov.hk</a>).<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700353_photo_1202688.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700353_photo_1202688.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Building services' engineering excellence at Wah Ha Estate wins professional recognition (with photos)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700296.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700296.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Housing Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In recognition of its demonstrated engineering excellence, Wah Ha Estate of the Hong Kong Housing Authority (HA) was granted the Project of the Year Award&nbsp;- Residential Building (2021) by the Chartered Institution of Building Services Engineers Hong Kong Region.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Wah Ha Estate was an extremely fast-tracked project in which the HA project team successfully converted the only remaining match box factory in Hong Kong to a sustainable public rental housing block in 2016, providing homes to 187 families after overcoming various site constraints.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;The competition focuses on actual measured performance outcomes, and not just design intent or performance specifications. This award recognises the HA&#39;s design, construction, installation, commissioning and operation of a low energy building,&quot; the Chief Building Services Engineer of the Housing Department, Mr Henry Chang, said today (November 17).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Government announced the conversion in 2012 with the aim of increasing the short term public housing supply and to preserve the only remaining H-shaped factory in Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;The biggest challenge for the project team was to provide affordable housing with a sustainable living environment from a Grade II historic building located within an industrial area, which is subject to considerable noise from nearby industrial buildings and transportation facilities, and at the same time maximise the development potential of the site as well as to conserve the historical value of the 55-year-old Chai Wan Factory Estate during the conversion,&quot; said Mr Chang.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The building design and the building services systems of Wah Ha Estate promote energy savings, address the needs of residents, and ensure that the building achieves the designed green targets by adopting various designs, some of which are unique in the HA&#39;s projects.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Lighting levels in lift lobbies, corridors and staircases in Wah Ha Estate can be enhanced by pressing either a manual button integrated with the door phone handset in a domestic flat or the manual switch at the&nbsp;lift lobby to suit residents&#39; needs.&nbsp;This can minimise&nbsp;energy consumption while meeting the requirement for barrier-free access.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;Apart from adopting daylight as much as possible and lighting sensor controls, energy efficient LED lighting was also installed in the estate. This is the first project of the HA to roll out LED lighting in public housing estates,&quot; Mr Chang said.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;High efficient gearless lifts were installed and an uninterrupted lift service can be maintained through a specially designed circuit arrangement in case of a temporary suspension of electricity during statutory periodic inspections of the electricity supply system.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A rainwater harvesting system (RWHS) was adopted to collect rainwater from the green roof of the building block, which can then be filtered and sterilised for irrigation purposes. The RWHS helps reduce dependence on the water supply and ease rainwater drainage.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;To mitigate the noise impact from railway and road traffic, the project team has incorporated a special acoustic balcony for flats in the vicinity of Chai Wan MTR Station.&nbsp;Habitable areas of those flats are also strategically oriented away from the noise sources of the MTR station and roads.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;To raise the awareness of residents on conservation of resources, electricity, water and gas consumption information is displayed on a 49-inch TV display panel at the lift lobby at the entrance of the housing block,&quot; said Mr Chang.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The HA engaged an&nbsp;independent consultant to conduct a resident survey about a year after the project&#39;s completion to gauge residents&#39; satisfaction levels as well as gather&nbsp;their opinions. The survey results in mid-2018 indicated a high level of satisfaction.<br />
&nbsp;<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202681.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202681.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202682.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202682.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202683.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202683.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202684.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202684.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202685.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202685.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202686.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202686.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202687.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700296_photo_1202687.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Online briefing for candidates of 2021 Legislative Council General Election to be held on Friday evening]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700341.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700341.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Electoral Affairs Commission:<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Electoral Affairs Commission (EAC) will hold an online briefing for candidates of the 2021 Legislative Council General Election (LCGE) at 7.30pm on Friday (November 19).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The EAC Chairman, Mr Justice Barnabas Fung Wah, will chair the briefing and brief candidates about the electoral arrangement for the LCGE, the guidelines on election-related activities and important points to note in running their election campaigns. A representative from the Independent Commission Against Corruption will explain the Elections (Corrupt and Illegal Conduct) Ordinance. A representative from Hongkong Post will explain the arrangement and requirements of the free postage service for election mail. Representatives from the Registration and Electoral Office and the Department of Justice will also be present.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Registration and Electoral Office has issued invitations to candidates and election agents for registration&nbsp;for the online briefing. Successfully registered candidates/election agents will receive login details and points to note. During the question-and-answer session of the briefing, questions submitted online by candidates/election agents will be randomly selected by a computer system.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Radio Television Hong Kong will provide a&nbsp;live broadcast of the briefing on RTHK TV 32 and the dedicated YouTube Channel (<a href="https://youtu.be/UJbCHcLQUJk" target="_blank">youtu.be/UJbCHcLQUJk</a>). The briefing will also be broadcast live on the website of the Information Services Department (<a href="http://webcast.info.gov.hk">webcast.info.gov.hk</a>). Relevant information on the briefing and the LCGE will be available at the election website (<a href="http://www.elections.gov.hk" target="_blank">www.elections.gov.hk</a>) for viewing by the candidates and the general public.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; For enquiries, please call the election hotline at 2891 1001 or email <a href="mailto:reoenq@reo.gov.hk">reoenq@reo.gov.hk</a>.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Auctions for Lunar New Year fair stalls in New Territories to start next Tuesday]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700370.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700370.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Food and Environmental Hygiene Department (FEHD) today (November 17) reminded interested parties to join auctions that will start next Tuesday (November 23) for stalls at the 2022 Lunar New Year (LNY) fairs in the New Territories.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The nine LNY fairs will be held at Kwai Chung Sports Ground in Kwai Tsing, Sha Tsui Road Playground in Tsuen Wan, Shek Wu Hui Playground in North District, Man Yee Playground in Sai Kung, Po Hong Park in Tseung Kwan O, Yuen Wo Playground in Sha Tin, Tin Hau Temple Fung Shui Square in Tai Po, Tung Tau Industrial Area Playground in Yuen Long, and Tin Hau Temple Plaza in Tuen Mun, with a total of 545 wet goods stalls. No dry goods stalls and fast food stalls will be provided at the venues. Except for Tin Hau Temple Plaza LNY fair in Tuen Mun, the auctions for stalls of these LNY fairs will be held at the Assembly Hall, 2/F, Lai Chi Kok Government Offices, 19 Lai Wan Road, Lai Chi Kok, Kowloon, from November 23 to December 2. The auction sessions are scheduled from 9.30am until completion of the auction.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The auction for stalls of Tin Hau Temple Plaza LNY fair in Tuen Mun will be held at Tseng Choi Street Community Hall, 27 Tseng Choi Street, Tuen Mun, on December 7. The auction session is scheduled from 9.30am until completion of the auction.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Details of the auctions, the number of stalls and opening prices are as follows:<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Kwai Chung Sports Ground (Kwai Tsing)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 23 (Tuesday)<br />
Number of stalls: 76<br />
Opening price: $410<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Sha Tsui Road Playground (Tsuen Wan)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 24 (Wednesday)<br />
Number of stalls: 96<br />
Opening price: $1,480<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Shek Wu Hui Playground (North District)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 25 (Thursday)<br />
Number of stalls: 72<br />
Opening price: $600<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Man Yee Playground (Sai Kung)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 26 (Friday)<br />
Number of stalls: 16<br />
Opening price: $320<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Po Hong Park (Tseung Kwan O)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 26 (Friday)<br />
Number of stalls: 54<br />
Opening price: $700<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Yuen Wo Playground (Sha Tin)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: November 29 (Monday)<br />
Number of stalls: 49<br />
Opening price: $2,990<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Tin Hau Temple Fung Shui Square (Tai Po)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: December 1 (Wednesday)<br />
Number of stalls: 46<br />
Opening price: $1,900<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Tung Tau Industrial Area Playground (Yuen Long)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: December 2 (Thursday)<br />
Number of stalls: 96<br />
Opening price: $590<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Tin Hau Temple Plaza (Tuen Mun)<br />
--------------------------------------------<br />
Auction date: December 7 (Tuesday)<br />
Number of stalls: 40<br />
Opening price: $1,250<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Bidders for LNY fair stalls must be at least 18 years old and ordinarily reside in Hong Kong. Persons entering the auction venues are required to comply with the measures for the prevention of COVID-19 to be implemented at the auction venues, which include body temperature screening to be conducted before entering the venues and masks to be worn at all times while inside the venues. On the auction day, except for exempted persons, all persons are required to scan the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; venue QR code using the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; mobile application on their phones before entering an auction venue. Exempted persons are required to complete a form to register their name, the first four digits or letters of their identification document, their contact number and the date and time of their visit. They are also required to present relevant identification documents for verification by the on-site staff.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Anyone can bid for more than one stall. A bidder must pay the bid price and register in person with his or her own name as the licensee of the stall immediately after successfully bidding for a stall. The bidder is also required to sign at once a licence agreement with the FEHD, or he/she will forfeit the rights to operate the stall.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Government may without cause postpone the commencement date and shorten the duration of the licensed period (including the duration for setting up stalls and the business period of the fair), or suspend or cancel the LNY fair wholly or in part. The bidding price (licence fee) paid will be refunded to the affected licensee on a pro-rata basis without interest. The licensee and his/her employees or agents must vacate the licenced area no later than the time specified by the Government verbally&nbsp;(by way of press release, public announcement or other similar communications) or in writing.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The FEHD reminded licensees that the stalls are solely for the purpose of selling and promoting the sale of the permitted commodities, and no other activities are allowed in the licensed area. If the FEHD considers that any activity conducted by the licensee to publicise, promote, display, show or sell any permitted commodities in the venue is unlawful, immoral or incompatible with the object of the LNY fair, the FEHD is entitled to direct the licensee to stop conducting such activity and the licensee must immediately comply with such direction.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Successful bidders shall comply with all the stipulations and provisions as set out in the licence agreement. Otherwise, the department is entitled to terminate the agreement and the licensee shall immediately vacate the stall.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Details of the 2022 LNY fairs such as the public notice, the locations and layouts of the fair venues, commodities allowed for sale at the fair stalls, open auction arrangements and related rules as well as a sample of the licence agreement are available at the FEHD website (<a href="https://www.fehd.gov.hk/english/index.html" target="_blank">www.fehd.gov.hk</a>). For enquiries, please call the FEHD hotline at 2868 0000.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Result of tenders of RMB Sovereign Bonds held on November 17, 2021]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700311.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700311.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​Result of the tenders of RMB Sovereign Bonds held on November 17, 2021:<br />
&nbsp;
<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="width:520px">Tender Result</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="height:17px; width:520px">*********************************************************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Tender Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Bonds available for Tender</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">2-year RMB Bonds</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Number</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">BCMKFB21002 (Re-open)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue and Settlement Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 19, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Maturity Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">September 27, 2023 (or the closest coupon payment date)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Coupon Rate</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">2.41 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Application Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 9,949 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 3,000 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Average Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">100.04</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Lowest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">99.93</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Highest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">100.75</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Allocation Ratio</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">Approximately 16.51 per cent</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;

<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="height:0px; width:520px">Tender Result</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="height:0px; width:520px">*********************************************************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Tender Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Bonds available for Tender</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">5-year RMB Bonds</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Number</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">BCMKFB21003 (Re-open)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue and Settlement Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 19, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Maturity Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">September 27, 2026 (or the closest coupon payment date)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Coupon Rate</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">2.50 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Application Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 6,636 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 2,000 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Average Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">99.70</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Lowest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">99.32</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Highest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">102.31</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Allocation Ratio</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">Approximately 41.00 per cent</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;

<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="height:0px; width:520px">Tender Result</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="height:0px; width:520px">*********************************************************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Tender Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Bonds available for Tender</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">15-year RMB Bonds<br />
			(Remaining tenor 10 years)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Number</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">BCMKFB16023 (Re-open)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue and Settlement Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">November 19, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Maturity Date</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">December 12, 2031 (or the closest coupon payment date)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Coupon Rate</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">4.15 per cent</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Application Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 3,173 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Issue Amount</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">RMB 1,000 million</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Average Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">112.27</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Lowest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">111.35</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Highest Accepted Price</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">119.52</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">&nbsp;</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">&nbsp;</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="height:0px; width:239px">Allocation Ratio</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:21px">:</td>
			<td style="height:0px; width:259px">Approximately 45.33 per cent</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
]]>			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Speech by CE at Hong Kong International Computer Conference 2021 Opening Ceremony (English only) (with photos/video)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700309.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700309.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 12:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Following is the speech by the Chief Executive, Mrs Carrie Lam, at the Hong Kong International Computer Conference 2021 Opening Ceremony today (November 17):&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;<br />
張志華部長 (Director General of the Youth Department of the Liaison Office of the Central People&#39;s Government in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR), Mr Zhang Zhihua), Rocky (President of the Hong Kong Computer Society, Dr Rocky Cheng), Peter (Chairperson of the Organising Committee of the Hong Kong International Computer Conference 2021, Mr Peter Yan), Professor Tam (Chairperson of the Programme Committee of the Hong Kong International Computer Conference 2021, Professor Tam Kar-yan), ladies and gentlemen,&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Good morning. I&#39;m delighted to have this welcome opportunity to address you at the 44th edition of the Hong Kong Computer Society&#39;s Hong Kong International Computer Conference.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Society&#39;s first conference dates all the way back to 1978. All these years, the Society has tirelessly hosted conferences to facilitate exchanges amongst industry professionals, researchers, government officials and educational practitioners from Hong Kong and from around the world in order to stay abreast of the endlessly accelerating speed and ubiquity of the ICT (information and communications technology) world, as well as to share invaluable insights and intelligence on ICT development and issues related to its application to benefit society. In this year&#39;s two-day conference, the Society has clearly captured the latest opportunities for ICT development by adopting the theme &quot;Emerging Technologies Shaping Our Future in the Greater Bay Area&quot;.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;For our overseas audience, Greater Bay Area stands for the Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Greater Bay Area, an economic region with a combined GDP of US$1.7 trillion, a total population of 86 million, and a per capita GDP of over US$19,000, whose further economic drive depends on innovation and technology (I&amp;T). Indeed, comprising nine Mainland cities and the two Special Administrative Regions of Hong Kong and Macao operating under the policy of &quot;One Country, Two Systems&quot;, and featuring different legal systems and complementary strengths, the Greater Bay Area itself is a highly innovative framework, within which technology and digitalisation will play a major role in bridging gaps and removing barriers.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Before the Outline Development Plan for the Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Greater Bay Area was promulgated in February 2019, the HKSAR Government had already placed innovation and technology high on our policy priorities. Over the past four years, we have invested more than HK$130 billion in I&amp;T development, and the results are encouraging. Our start-ups today number about 3 800. That&#39;s 68 per cent more than just four years ago. During the same period, the number of employees in our start-ups has more than doubled to about 14 000. Investors have responded no less enthusiastically to our growing start-up community. Venture capital investment last year increased to HK$10 billion, up&nbsp;8 per cent as compared to 2017. In addition, according to relevant market research, the gross floor area of data centres in Hong Kong has increased from about 465 000 square metres in 2015 to about 743 000 square metres in 2019, representing an average annual growth rate of around 10 per cent. And I must add, all these achievements took place during an unprecedented period of over two and a half years with the social riots that we have seen in the latter part of 2019 and almost two years of the COVID-19 pandemic.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Greater Bay Area&#39;s relentless rise will only boost those numbers. Under the Outline Development Plan for the Greater Bay Area, the Area will be developed into an international innovation and technology hub, and Hong Kong will play a major part in it. Furthermore, the National 14th Five-Year Plan promulgated in March this year offers clear and compelling support for Hong Kong&#39;s development in eight areas, with I&amp;T included in the national plan for the first time.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;It is crucial for us to make the most out of the opportunities ahead of us. In my Policy Address delivered last month, I announced a number of groundbreaking measures to fast-track Hong Kong&#39;s I&amp;T development. A particularly far-reaching proposal is to build the Northern Metropolis, which takes up 300 square kilometres of Hong Kong land and it is along the Hong Kong-Shenzhen boundary. Within the Metropolis, the Hong Kong-Shenzhen Innovation and Technology Park in the Lok Ma Chau Loop and the surrounding areas will be integrated to form the San Tin Technopole. That will give us about 240 hectares to work with, not only for R&amp;D, but also for advanced manufacturing activities. To give you a feel, the 240 hectares of land for this purpose is almost equivalent to the total area of the three industrial parks now in Hong Kong. Along with the Shenzhen Innovation and Technology Zone across the river, it will come together as the Shenzhen-Hong Kong I&amp;T Co-operation Zone&nbsp;- the central engine for the high-powered development of an international innovation and technology hub in the Greater Bay Area. In addition, we will set aside about five hectares of land in a place called Lau Fau Shan for landmark I&amp;T facilities on a scale comparable to that of Cyberport. In total, we expect that the Northern Metropolis will provide 650 000 jobs, including 150 000 in the I&amp;T sector.&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;We will also continue to expand the Hong Kong Science Park. For this purpose, we will take forward the Ma Liu Shui reclamation project and vacate the site of the Sha Tin Sewage Treatment Works, providing another 88 hectares of dedicated land for I&amp;T purposes. The Cyberport 5 project has also commenced, which will increase the gross floor area of Cyberport by more than 40 per cent within four years&#39; time.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Since the release of my 2021 Policy Address, I have received very positive feedback on the proposals but almost all industry professionals point to the desperate need for talents, particularly the nurturing of local talents. In the past few years, the Government has implemented various measures to support STEM (science, technology, engineering and mathematics) education in schools, including updating the curriculum, strengthening training for teachers, providing financial and other support, and organising large-scale learning activities. Hopefully that will help produce a steady supply of talents for I&amp;T development in Hong Kong. But school education should be complemented by exposure and activities outside the school, and I look to the Hong Kong Computer Society to support our endeavours in nurturing young talents and start-ups on all fronts.<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Finally, my thanks to the Hong Kong Computer Society and its more than 9 000 members for the excellent efforts in promoting I&amp;T and ICT development and application in Hong Kong. I wish you a rewarding conference and the best of health and business in the coming year. Thank you very much.<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700309_photo_1202547.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700309_photo_1202547.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700309_photo_1202548.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111700309_photo_1202548.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Digital Realty opens second data centre in Hong Kong (with photo)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111600523.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111600523.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​Digital Realty, one of the largest global providers of carrier- and cloud-neutral data centre, colocation and interconnection solutions, officially opened its second data centre in Hong Kong today (November 17). Digital Realty Kin Chuen (HKG11) will leverage the city&#39;s strategic location to tap into the region&#39;s fast-growing demand for data storage.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The multi-storey data centre is strategically located in Hong Kong&#39;s developing data centre cluster in Kwai Chung, spans 21 000 square metres and can deliver up to 24 megawatts of critical information technology capacity. It is expected to support the development of Hong Kong as a data hub on PlatformDIGITAL, Digital Realty&#39;s first-of-its-kind global data centre platform for scaling digital business, and drive the adoption of cloud computing services and solutions in the region.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Chief Executive Officer of Digital Realty, Mr A William Stein, said, &quot;Hong Kong is an international financial and trade hub in the region and represents a key connectivity gateway between Asia-Pacific and the rest of the world for global enterprises. The opening of our second data centre in Hong Kong today is set to deliver greater coverage, capacity and connectivity capabilities to meet the growing demand from enterprises looking to scale their digital footprint across Asia-Pacific and beyond.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Managing Director for APAC at Digital Realty, Mr Mark Smith, said, &quot;We can expect the volume of data exchange and the corresponding demand for data centre services in Hong Kong to continue their upward trajectories over the next few years. Our new facility today comes at an opportune moment and will go a long way towards supporting the digital aspirations of our customers in China, the broader Asia-Pacific region and globally.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Associate Director-General of Investment Promotion Mr Charles Ng congratulated Digital Realty on the opening of its new data centre in Hong Kong. He said, &quot;Hong Kong as an international business hub has sophisticated high-tech infrastructure, tech professionals, reliable power supply, and robust enforcement of data privacy and security. It is an ideal location for data centre operators, like Digital Realty, to expand in the region.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
About Digital Realty<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Digital Realty supports the world&#39;s leading enterprises and service providers by delivering the full spectrum of data centre, colocation and interconnection solutions. PlatformDIGITAL, the company&#39;s global data centre platform, provides customers with a trusted foundation and proven Pervasive Datacenter Architecture solution methodology for scaling digital business and efficiently managing data gravity challenges. Digital Realty&#39;s global data centre footprint gives customers access to the connected communities that matter to them with 291 facilities in 47 metros across 24 countries on six continents. For more information, please visit <a href="https://www.digitalrealty.com/" target="_blank">digitalrealty.com</a>.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
About Invest Hong Kong<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Invest Hong Kong is the department of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region Government responsible for attracting foreign direct investment and supporting overseas and Mainland businesses to set up or expand in Hong Kong. It provides free advice and customised services for overseas and Mainland companies. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.investhk.gov.hk/" target="_blank">www.investhk.gov.hk</a>.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For a photo, please visit: <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/investhk/albums/72157720112276242" target="_blank">www.flickr.com/photos/investhk/albums/72157720112276242</a>.<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111600523_photo_1202512.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/17/P2021111600523_photo_1202512.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Red flags hoisted at some beaches]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700224.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700224.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:22:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[Attention TV/radio announcers:<br />
<br />
Please broadcast the following as soon as possible:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Here is an item of interest to swimmers.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Leisure and Cultural Services Department announced today (November 17) that due to big waves, red flags have been hoisted at Stanley Main Beach and Big Wave Bay Beach in Southern District, Hong Kong Island; and Clear Water Bay Second Beach in Sai Kung District. Beachgoers are advised not to swim at these beaches.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hongkong Post unveils new stamp issues from January to June 2022]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111600700.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111600700.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​Hongkong Post today (November 17) announced the six sets of special stamps to be issued from January to June 2022, offering a fantastic collection of stamps under a variety of themes, each with its distinctive and refreshing style.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The coming issues cover a wide range of themes, namely national development, international events and local culture. Among them, the most exciting one is the &quot;Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Greater Bay Area Development&quot; special stamps that will be issued on February 18, 2022 (Friday). The Greater Bay Area comprises the two Special Administrative Regions of Hong Kong and Macao, and the nine municipalities in Guangdong Province. The development of the Greater Bay Area is accorded the status of key strategic planning in the Country&#39;s development blueprint. Hong Kong will hold the valuable opportunities and participate proactively in the in-depth integration within the region and development of an international first-class bay area ideal for living, working and travelling.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Equally attractive is the stamp sheetlet on &quot;China&#39;s Aerospace Development&quot; depicting the milestones of China&#39;s Aerospace Development since the 1970s. The stamp sheetlet is designed in an oval shape of the universe. It contains two round-shaped stamps symbolising the view of the aerospace from the spaceship.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hongkong Post, as usual, will issue a set of special stamps on the Chinese zodiac sign of the coming year to herald the Lunar New Year. &quot;Year of the Tiger&quot; stamp depicts the Tiger in diversified art forms. A &quot;Gold and Silver Stamp Sheetlet on Lunar New Year Animals &ndash; Ox/Tiger&quot; will also be issued, featuring a Year of the Ox stamp and a Year of the Tiger stamp in pairs in celebration of the festive season.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;After the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games and the Paralympic Games, the XXIV Olympic Winter Games Beijing 2022 will be held in February 2022. This is the first time for China to host the Winter Games and Hongkong Post will specifically bring forward a set of stamps featuring the various sport events, rekindling the community&#39;s Olympic enthusiasm.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Following the enthusiastic response&nbsp;to the &quot;Local Snacks in Hong Kong&quot; special stamps issued in 2021, stamp lovers must keep an eye for &quot;Local Snacks in Hong Kong II&quot; which will bring forth another set of Hong Kong style local snacks and the most authentic manifestation of local food culture.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Located at the western tip of the West Kowloon Cultural District, the Hong Kong Palace Museum is scheduled to open in mid-2022. Embracing new curatorial approaches, the Museum will offer a Hong Kong perspective and a global vision, presenting the finest objects from the Palace Museum and other leading cultural institutions around the world. The special stamps under the theme of &quot;Hong Kong Palace Museum&quot; showcase the precious collections from the Palace Museum. The public can take the precious collections home in the form of philatelic products for appreciation, or introduce the collections to overseas friends and relatives through the special stamps.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customers may place advance orders for the above new stamp products from today on the Hongkong Post Stamps website (<a href="https://stamps.hongkongpost.hk/" target="_blank">stamps.hongkongpost.hk</a>) or the Facebook page &quot;郵票．郵趣@Hongkong Post Stamps&quot; (<a href="http://www.facebook.com/HKPStamps" target="_blank">www.facebook.com/HKPStamps</a>). Those who place orders by December 6 (Monday) will receive attractive gifts and bonus points. Further information is available at the Hongkong Post Stamps website or by calling the Hongkong Post Philatelic Bureau hotline at 2785 5711 for enquiry.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[LD organises online exhibition on Employment Ordinance and Minimum Wage Ordinance]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111100573.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111100573.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Labour Department (LD) has launched a two-day online exhibition from 9am today (November 17) to 6pm tomorrow (November 18) at the LD&#39;s website disseminating information about the Employment Ordinance and the Minimum Wage Ordinance to enhance the public&#39;s understanding of employment rights and benefits.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Consolidating the content of physical exhibitions held by the LD, the online exhibition features the main provisions of the Employment Ordinance and the Minimum Wage Ordinance, employment rights and benefits for foreign domestic helpers, as well as good human resource management measures.&nbsp;The relevant hyperlink is&nbsp;<a href="https://www.labour.gov.hk/Online_exhibition_EO_MWO/index_en.html" target="_blank">www.labour.gov.hk/Online_exhibition_EO_MWO/index_en.html</a>.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Person who visited eighth floor of Immigration Tower in Wan Chai tested preliminary positive for COVID-19]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700018.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/17/P2021111700018.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Immigration Department (ImmD) today (November 17) said the department was notified by the Centre for Health Protection (CHP) yesterday (November 16) that an applicant who visited the eighth floor of the Immigration Tower in Wan Chai on November 5 for registration of identity card had been tested preliminary positive for COVID-19.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The ImmD completed thorough cleaning and sterilisation at the eighth floor of the Immigration Tower&nbsp;in accordance with the CHP&#39;s advice, and arranged staff of the concerned offices to undergo COVID-19 testing.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;During the situation of COVID-19 infection, the ImmD has been strictly implementing various disease prevention measures, including measuring the body temperature of and providing alcohol-based handrub to all persons before their entry into the building, providing employees with masks and other protective equipments, requiring employees to wear masks when performing duties, and stepping up the cleaning and sterilising measures for the working environment.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The department will continue to maintain close liaison with the CHP, actively co-operate with CHP&#39;s quarantine arrangements. The ImmD has also reminded its staff to pay attention to personal hygiene and stay vigilant. Staff have been reminded to seek medical advice and inform the department as soon as possible if feeling unwell.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Government gazettes compulsory testing notice]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111700378.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111700378.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;​The Government exercises the power under the Prevention and Control of Disease (Compulsory Testing for Certain Persons) Regulation (Cap. 599J) and publishes in the Gazette a compulsory testing notice, which requires any person who had been present at 38 specified premises during the specified period (persons subject to compulsory testing) to undergo a COVID-19 nucleic acid test.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In view of two preliminary positive imported cases who had stayed in Hong Kong during the incubation period, 29 specified premises are included in the compulsory testing notice. Also, in relation to three previous imported cases who had stayed in Hong Kong during the incubation period, any person who had been present at four specified premises during the specified period has to undergo additional testing. The Government strongly reminds members of the public to strictly follow the compulsory testing requirements and undergo the multiple tests on time as required. The above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well. They are advised to closely monitor their health conditions. They should seek medical attention and undergo testing even they have only mild symptoms.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Furthermore, since there was an outbreak of upper respiratory tract infection and/or influenza-like illness in five schools, and the symptoms of the diseases concerned are similar to those of COVID-19, for prudence&#39;s sake, the relevant schools or their specified levels are covered in the compulsory testing notice. Persons who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course would be taken to have complied with the requirements set out in the compulsory testing notice.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Persons subject to compulsory testing in accordance with a compulsory testing notice must go to any of the mobile specimen collection stations, community testing centres (CTCs) or recognised local medical testing institutions to undergo professional swab sampling in fulfilling the requirements for compulsory testing. Young children may continue to undergo the test using a stool specimen.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; If Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 3 or above, the Red or Black Rainstorm Warning Signal or the post-super typhoon &quot;extreme conditions&quot; announcement by the Government is in force at any time during the period for undergoing the compulsory testing, the period for undergoing the compulsory testing will be further extended for one day.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Comirnaty and CoronaVac vaccines are highly effective in preventing severe cases and deaths from COVID-19. They can provide protection to those vaccinated to prevent serious complications and even death after infection. The Government appeals to persons who are not yet vaccinated, especially senior citizens, chronic patients and other immunocompromised persons who face a higher chance of death after COVID-19 infection, to get vaccinated as soon as possible for better self-protection before the fifth wave strikes in Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Details of the compulsory testing notice are in Annex 1.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Subsequent to the announcement by the Centre for Health Protection (CHP) on the updated quarantine arrangements of local COVID-19 cases with a mutant strain, persons who resided or worked within the same building as the residence of relevant cases will be subject to compulsory testing on specified dates in accordance with the announcement by the Department of Health (DH). They will also be required to undergo self-monitoring until the 21st day (see the details of the buildings and dates of testing at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/CTN_Specified_premises_and_Dates_of_Testing.pdf" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/CTN_Specified_premises_and_Dates_of_Testing.pdf</a>). For prudence&#39;s sake, the above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In accordance with the compulsory testing notice issued earlier, all household members of close contacts are required to undergo compulsory testing. Any person who had lived with a person placed under quarantine pursuant to section 22 of the Prevention and Control of Disease Regulation (Cap. 599A) (person under quarantine) in the same residential unit on the date of commencement of quarantine or during the 14 days before that day, and who becomes aware of the quarantine of the person under quarantine when the relevant quarantine has not yet been completed, has to undergo testing within two days of him or her becoming aware that the person under quarantine has been placed under quarantine and report to the Government the result of the test by phone (6275 6901), fax (2530 5872) or email (<a href="mailto:ct@csb.gov.hk" target="_blank">ct@csb.gov.hk</a>) within three days of undergoing the test. For prudence&#39;s sake, the above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; CTCs provide testing services for the public, including free service for persons subject to compulsory testing. Booking and walk-in services are available. Members of the public only need to provide simple personal information on the 24-hour booking system (<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en</a>). The system shows the booking status of the centres for the coming two weeks to facilitate the public&#39;s planning and selection of a suitable testing centre and a time slot for testing. The testing centres will accord priority to serve individuals with advance bookings. As of 6pm today (November 16), there were around 33 000 booking places available for tomorrow (November 17) at the CTCs, and around 93 per cent availability for booking places for the coming seven days. Members of the public may call the testing centres for enquiries on the availability of bookings or walk-in quotas before visiting the centres.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Government will set up mobile specimen collection trucks in Kwai Tsing District and Sha Tin District, and mobile specimen collection stations at the following locations tomorrow for persons subject to compulsory testing for free:<br />
&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Amphitheatre, Hing Man Estate in Chai Wan</li>
	<li>Podium playground, New Jade Garden in Chai Wan</li>
	<li>Carpark of Ocean Court in Aberdeen</li>
	<li>Open area outside G/F, King Tai Court in San Po Kong</li>
	<li>Staff carpark of Hong Kong Disneyland Park</li>
</ul>
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Outdoor mobile specimen collection stations will be closed if Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 3 or the Red Rainstorm Warning Signal is in force while all mobile specimen collection stations together with all CTCs will be closed when Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 8 or higher or the Black Rainstorm Warning Signal is in force.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coupled with all CTCs, there will be a total of 33 CTCs/mobile specimen collection stations in various districts tomorrow to provide free service for persons subject to compulsory testing. The testing capacity should be sufficient to meet the demand. The opening dates and operating hours of the mobile specimen collection stations in various districts providing free COVID-19 nucleic acid testing services for the general public are stated in Annex 2. Persons subject to compulsory testing and those with the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; COVID-19 exposure notification or SMS notification from the CHP reminding them to undergo testing as soon as possible may receive free testing at CTCs or mobile specimen collection stations (if the service scope is applicable).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Persons subject to compulsory testing may choose to undergo testing via the following routes:<br />
&nbsp;<br />
1. To visit any of the mobile specimen collection stations (see the list and target groups (if applicable) at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html</a>) for testing;<br />
2. To attend any of the CTCs (see the list at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en</a>);<br />
3. To self-arrange testing provided by private laboratories which are recognised by the DH and can issue SMS notifications in respect of test results (see the list at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/List_of_recognised_laboratories_RTPCR.pdf" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/List_of_recognised_laboratories_RTPCR.pdf</a>), and the relevant sample must be taken through combined nasal and throat swabs; or<br />
4. To use a specimen bottle distributed to the relevant specified premises by the CHP (if applicable), and return the specimen bottle with the stool sample collected as per relevant guidelines.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; If a person subject to compulsory testing obtains a medical certificate issued by a registered medical practitioner, proving that he or she is unfit to undergo testing using a sample taken through combined nasal and throat swabs because of health reasons, then he or she may choose to undergo testing via the following routes by providing a deep throat saliva sample:<br />
1. To obtain a deep throat saliva specimen collection pack from any of the 121 post offices, vending machines set up at 20 MTR stations or 47 designated general out-patient clinics (GOPCs) of the Hospital Authority and return the specimen to one of the designated specimen collection points (see the distribution points and times, and the specimen collection points and times, at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html</a>);<br />
2. To undergo testing at any of the GOPCs of the Hospital Authority as instructed by a medical professional of the Hospital Authority; or<br />
3. To self-arrange testing provided by private laboratories which are recognised by the DH and can issue SMS notifications in respect of test results.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; A spokesman for the Food and Health Bureau cautioned that testing received at the Accident and Emergency Departments of the Hospital Authority or during hospital stays, or testing provided by private laboratories which cannot issue SMS notifications in respect of test results, does not comply with the requirements of the aforementioned compulsory testing notice.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &quot;If persons subject to compulsory testing have symptoms, they should seek medical attention immediately and undergo testing as instructed by a medical professional. They should not attend the mobile specimen collection stations or the CTCs.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Persons subject to compulsory testing must keep the SMS notifications containing the result of the test and the relevant medical certificate (if applicable) for checking by a law enforcement officer when the officer requires the persons to provide information about their undergoing the specified test.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Furthermore, persons subject to testing under the compulsory testing notices should, as far as reasonably practicable, take appropriate personal disease prevention measures including wearing a mask and maintaining hand hygiene, and, unless for the purpose of undergoing the specified test, stay at their place of residence and avoid going out until the test result is ascertained as far as possible.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Any enquiries on compulsory testing arrangements may be addressed to the hotline at 6275 6901, which operates daily from 9am to 6pm. If persons subject to compulsory testing plan to conduct testing at any of the CTCs, they can check the centre&#39;s appointment status in advance. The hotlines of the CTCs are available at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en/info" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en/info</a>.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Government will continue to trace possibly infected persons who had been to the relevant premises, and seriously verify whether they had complied with the testing notices. Any person who fails to comply with the testing notices commits an offence and may be fined a fixed penalty of $5,000. The person would also be issued with a compulsory testing order requiring him or her to undergo testing within a specified time frame. Failure to comply with the order is an offence and the offender would be liable to a fine at level 4 ($25,000) and imprisonment for six months.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Relevant officers of different government departments are empowered to perform certain functions under the relevant Regulations under the Prevention and Control of Disease Ordinance (Cap. 599), including requesting individuals to provide information and assistance when necessary. Any person who fails to comply with the relevant request commits an offence and would be liable to a fine at level 3 ($10,000). Collection and use of any personal data for conducting COVID-19 tests must meet the requirements under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486). Government departments or testing service providers which handle the relevant information may provide the data to the DH or other relevant departments for anti-epidemic purposes as necessary. The workflow does not involve the provision of any personal data to organisations or persons outside Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The spokesman said, &quot;The Government urges all individuals who are in doubt about their own health conditions, or individuals with infection risks (such as individuals who visited places with epidemic outbreaks or contacted confirmed cases), to undergo testing promptly for early identification of infected persons.&quot;&nbsp;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Alliance for Green Commercial Banks organises 3rd Roundtable in Climate Risk (with photo)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600569.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600569.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority:&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Alliance for Green Commercial Banks (the Alliance), co-launched by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) and the International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, hosted the third roundtable, &quot;Climate Risk in Action: A Conversation with Practitioners&quot;, virtually today (November 16).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Alliance was jointly launched by the HKMA and the IFC in November 2020 to help banks develop the solutions needed to address climate change across emerging markets. As part of its knowledge sharing and capacity building efforts, the Alliance has been hosting a series of roundtable sessions on relevant topics. The series of roundtable sessions will equip participants with the knowledge related to green banking transition and will provide a platform for market participants across commercial banks, leading real sector companies, tech innovators, thought leaders, and regulators to share their first-hand experiences and intelligence.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The third roundtable commenced with opening remarks from the Chief Investment Officer and the Global Head of Climate Finance, Financial Institutions Group, IFC, Mr Peter Cashion; and a keynote by the Regional Director, CDP Hong Kong, Ms Pratima Divgi.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The panel discussion was moderated by the Executive Director (Banking Policy) of the HKMA,&nbsp;Mr Daryl Ho, and featured the following speakers:<br />
&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>the Head of Client Markets of Southeast Asia, India, Korea, Hong Kong and Taiwan, P&amp;C Reinsurance Asia, Swiss Re, Mr Victor Kuk;</li>
	<li>the Head of the Climate Change Centre of Excellence and Global Head of ESG Research, the Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation Limited, Mr Chan Wai-shin; and</li>
	<li>the Executive Director -&nbsp;Issuer Business, V.E, part of Moody&#39;s ESG Solutions, Ms Juliette Macresy.</li>
</ul>
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;During the discussion, speakers unveiled the current strategies, as well as the opportunities and challenges in climate risk management.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&quot;At IFC we embrace responsible investing by helping banks manage climate-related physical and transition risk associated with the projects and businesses they are funding, by developing a common assessment framework to help banks to assess their individual &#39;greenness baseline&#39;,&quot; said Mr Cashion.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&quot;To address a global issue like climate change, concerted efforts of different stakeholders is of paramount importance. Today&#39;s discussion has demonstrated how the financial sector can make critical contribution to strengthening the global response to climate change,&quot; said Mr Ho.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riding on the success, the Alliance will be hosting roundtable sessions in the coming future. Participants will have the opportunity to learn and exchange knowledge with global sustainability as well as environmental, social and governance (ESG) experts, leaders in green finance and real sector, and peers from across the regions on topics such as green finance, carbon neutrality, climate risk, ESG, market trends and opportunities, policy environment and more.<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600569_photo_1202513.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600569_photo_1202513.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Several prepackaged food samples in breach of food labelling regulation]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600697.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600697.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Centre for Food Safety (CFS) of the Food and Environmental Hygiene Department announced today (November 16) that a sample of prepackaged dates, a sample of prepackaged preserved cabbage and a sample of prepackaged bamboo fungi were found to contain sulphur dioxide, a preservative which is allowed to be used in certain foods, but the functional class and name of the additive were not declared on the food labels. Members of the public should not consume the affected batches of products. The trade should also stop using or selling the affected batches of products immediately if they possess them.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Product details are as follows:<br />
<br />
Product name: Chinese Date<br />
Brand: Green dot dot<br />
Place of origin: China<br />
Net weight: 350 grams<br />
Distributor: Organic Gardens International Limited (recall hotline: 3181 4488)<br />
Best-before date: July 23, 2022<br />
<br />
Product name: Tianjin Preserved Vegetable<br />
Brand: (not available in English)<br />
Place of origin: China<br />
Net weight: 300 grams<br />
Distributor: Golden Long Food Trading Limited (recall hotline: 2566 3007)<br />
Best-before date: December 31, 2022<br />
<br />
Product name: (not available in English)<br />
Brand: Kai&#39;s Gourmet<br />
Place of origin: China<br />
Net weight: 38 grams<br />
Importer: Kairun Food HK Ltd. (recall hotline: 3483 0098)<br />
Best-before date: July 30, 2022<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;The CFS collected the above-mentioned dates, preserved cabbage and bamboo fungi samples from a department store in Hung Hom, a supermarket in Mong Kok and an online shop for testing under its routine Food Surveillance Programme. The test results showed that the samples contained sulphur dioxide. Although the sulphur dioxide levels are below the maximum permitted level under the Preservatives in Food Regulation (Cap. 132BD), the functional class and name of the additive were not declared on the food labels of the samples,&quot; a CFS spokesman said.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;The CFS has informed the vendors concerned of the irregularities, and instructed them to stop sale and remove from shelves the affected batches of products. The above-mentioned distributors/ importer have initiated a recall according to the CFS&#39; instructions. Members of the public may call the respective hotlines above during office hours for enquiries about the recall,&quot; the spokesman added.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sulphur dioxide is a preservative which can be used in a variety of foods including dried vegetables, dried fruits, pickled vegetables and salted fish products. Sulphur dioxide is water soluble, and most of it can be removed through washing and cooking. However, susceptible individuals who are allergic to this preservative may experience breathing difficulties, headache and nausea after consumption.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The spokesman reminded the food trade that the use of preservatives in food must comply with the Preservatives in Food Regulation (Cap. 132BD). Furthermore, the Food and Drugs (Composition and Labelling) Regulations (Cap. 132W) require that for all prepackaged food for sale in Hong Kong containing sulphite in a concentration of 10 ppm or more, the functional class of the sulphite and its name shall be specified in the list of ingredients. Offenders are liable to a maximum fine of $50,000 and six months&#39; imprisonment upon conviction.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The CFS will alert the trade, continue to follow up on the incident and take appropriate action. Investigation is ongoing.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Premium waived for pedestrian link in Hung Hom]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600651.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600651.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Government announced today (November 16) that the Chief Executive in Council has approved a premium waiver for a pedestrian link in Hung Hom (location plan at Annex).<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A spokesperson for the Development Bureau (DEVB) said that the proposed pedestrian link would connect the covered walkway network of Hung Hom MTR station to a nearby hotel development. It would provide a barrier-free public passageway to Cheong Tung Road at ground level, which would also offer an alternative route for members of the public to travel, via Cheong Tung Road, to the area where a number of funeral parlours are located. The proposed pedestrian link and its connecting path would provide better walking conditions when compared with the existing non-weather proof access via Cheong Wan Road where pedestrians also have to cross a road junction. The proposal would enhance the connectivity and walkability of the area as a whole.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;In accordance with the evaluation mechanism under the Policy of Facilitating Provision of Pedestrian Links by the Private Sector, the DEVB considered that the above pedestrian link could bring public benefits in multiple aspects, including providing an alternative choice to the existing routes with less desirable walking conditions and strengthening the area-wide walking network, etc.&nbsp;The Land and Development Advisory Committee has been consulted earlier.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Under the Policy, the applicant will be required to shoulder the design, construction, management and maintenance responsibilities and related costs of the pedestrian link, and provide 24-hour barrier-free public access at the completed pedestrian link.&nbsp;The applicant will also need to work on other issues related to the implementation of the pedestrian link such as design, visual impact assessment, gazettal and objection resolution, etc.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The spokesperson said that other interested parties are welcome to contact the DEVB on the details of the Policy.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Judiciary severely condemns intimidations against judicial officers]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600656.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600656.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Judiciary:<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Judiciary today (November 16) expressed grave concerns about recent repeated incidents involving intimidating letters sent to judicial officers.&nbsp;The cases have been reported to the Police.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Judiciary stressed that attempts to exert improper pressure on Judges and Judicial Officers (JJOs) represent a direct challenge to the rule of law and the principle of judicial independence. They must be severely condemned.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;As stated in express terms in the Basic Law, the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR) enjoys independent judicial power, including that of final adjudication. The courts of the HKSAR shall exercise judicial power independently, free from any interference.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Judiciary reiterated that, according to the judicial oath, JJOs must handle cases in accordance with the law to ensure the due administration of justice, safeguard the law and administer justice without fear or favour, self-interest or deceit. Judges must decide cases fearlessly, independently and professionally in accordance with the law and legal principles, regardless of whether they involve controversial laws or social events, or whether the outcomes are popular or likely to attract criticisms. Those who are dissatisfied with the verdict or sentence may seek an appeal under the existing mechanism.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Cluster of Vancomycin Resistant Enterococci cases at Tuen Mun Hospital]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600431.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600431.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hospital Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The spokesperson for Tuen Mun Hospital (TMH) made the following announcement today (November 16):<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Two male patients (aged 72 and 76) in a medical and geriatrics ward of TMH were confirmed to be carrying Vancomycin Resistant Enterococci (VRE) on November 4.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In accordance with the prevailing infection control guidelines, the hospital has conducted contact tracing for the index patient. Seven more male patients (aged 53 to 70) were found to be VRE carriers but without clinical symptoms. Among the nine patients, two patients are still hospitalised with stable condition. One patient has passed away due to his underlying diseases. The remaining six patients have already been discharged.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The ward concerned has adopted the following enhanced infection control measures:<br />
&nbsp;<br />
1.&nbsp;Enhanced hand hygiene and stringent contact precautions;<br />
2.&nbsp;Enhanced attention to contamination-prone procedures; and<br />
3.&nbsp;Enhanced disinfection and cleaning of the concerned ward.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The hospital will continue the enhanced infection control measures and closely monitor the situation of the ward. The cases have been reported to the Hospital Authority Head Office and the Centre for Health Protection for necessary follow-up.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[CHP investigates two suspected food poisoning clusters]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600619.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600619.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Centre for Health Protection (CHP) of the Department of Health is today (November 16) investigating two suspected food poisoning clusters affecting&nbsp;seven persons, and reminded the public to maintain personal, food and environmental hygiene to prevent food-borne diseases.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The first cluster involved two females, aged 56 and 60, who developed abdominal pain, diarrhoea and vomiting about 3.5 hours after having dinner at a restaurant in Mong Kok on November 12.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The other cluster involved five females, aged 26 to 28, who developed similar symptoms about 39.5 hours after having dinner at the same restaurant on November 13.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Two of the affected persons sought medical advice and none required hospitalisation. All of them are in stable condition.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&quot;We have alerted the Food and Environmental Hygiene Department to the incident and investigations are ongoing,&quot; a spokesman for the CHP said.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;To prevent food-borne diseases, members of the public are reminded to maintain personal, food and environmental hygiene at all times. When dining out:<br />
&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Patronise only reliable and licensed restaurants;</li>
	<li>Avoid eating raw seafood;</li>
	<li>Be a discerning consumer in choosing cold dishes, including sashimi, sushi and raw oysters, at a buffet;</li>
	<li>Ensure food is thoroughly cooked before eating during a hot pot or barbecue meal;</li>
	<li>Handle raw and cooked foods carefully and separate them completely during the cooking process;</li>
	<li>Use two sets of chopsticks and utensils to handle raw and cooked food;</li>
	<li>Do not patronise illegal food hawkers;</li>
	<li>Drink boiled water;</li>
	<li>Do not try to use salt, vinegar, wine and wasabi to kill bacteria as they are not effective; and</li>
	<li>Always wash hands before eating and after going to the toilet.</li>
</ul>
]]>			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Customs detects speedboat smuggling case involving about $10 million (with photos)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600567.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600567.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​Hong Kong Customs yesterday (November 15) mounted an anti-smuggling operation and detected a suspected speedboat smuggling case in the waters off Lamma Island. About 930 kilograms of suspected smuggled dried sea cucumbers and about 890kg of suspected smuggled lobsters with a total estimated market value of about $10 million were seized.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customs officers yesterday conducted an anti-smuggling operation at Aberdeen Typhoon Shelter and spotted a suspicious speedboat loaded with goods. The officers then took action and the speedboat immediately proceeded at a high speed towards the south-western waters of Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customs officers subsequently intercepted the speedboat in the waters off Lamma Island and seized the batch of suspected smuggled goods on board the speedboat.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;During the operation, Customs arrested two men aged 40 and 45 suspected to be in connection with the case. A speedboat and two high-power outboard engines were also detained.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;An investigation is ongoing.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customs stresses that it will keep up its enforcement action and will continue to fiercely combat sea smuggling activities by proactive risk-management and intelligence-based enforcement strategies. Targeted anti-smuggling operations at suitable times will also be mounted to land a solid blow against relevant activities.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Smuggling is a serious offence. Under the Import and Export Ordinance, any person found guilty of importing or exporting unmanifested cargo is liable to a maximum fine of $2 million and imprisonment for seven years.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Members of the public may report any suspected smuggling activities to Customs&#39; 24-hour hotline 2545 6182 or its dedicated crime-reporting email account (<a href="mailto:crimereport@customs.gov.hk">crimereport@customs.gov.hk</a>).<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202515.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202515.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202516.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202516.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202517.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202517.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202518.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202518.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202519.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600567_photo_1202519.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[DH's Temporary Specimen Collection Centre Two at Hong Kong International Airport to commence operation on November 18]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600500.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600500.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​The Department of Health (DH) announced today (November 16) that Temporary Specimen Collection Centre Two (TSCC-2) set up by the DH at the T1 Satellite Concourse of Hong Kong International Airport (HKIA) will commence operation on November 18. Together with the current Temporary Specimen Collection Centre One (TSCC-1) set up at the T1 Midfield Concourse, travellers arriving from places of different risk levels can be effectively segregated.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starting from November 18, TSCC-2 will be dedicated for travellers arriving in&nbsp;Hong Kong from the Mainland via the airport, while TSCC-1 will handle travellers arriving in Hong Kong from Taiwan and overseas areas.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Currently, all travellers arriving in Hong Kong via HKIA are required to proceed to the TSCC at HKIA immediately upon arrival. Combined nasal and throat swabs will be collected from the travellers by dedicated staff for COVID-19 nucleic acid testing. They are required to stay at the TSCC to wait for test results before they can proceed with immigration procedures (&quot;test and hold&quot;).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A spokesman for the DH reiterated that amid the severe pandemic situation across the world, the Government strives to protect public health and at the same time foster favourable conditions for resuming cross-boundary travel with the Mainland and cross-border travel in future. To this end, the various anti-epidemic measures to prevent the importation of cases and the spreading of the virus in the community should be kept up.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Auction for Victoria Park Lunar New Year Fair stalls ends]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600529.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600529.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The open auction for stalls at the 2022 Victoria Park Lunar New Year (LNY) Fair concluded today (November 16). The total revenue was $4,510,440 compared with $2,462,320 last year.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;A spokesman for the Food and Environmental Hygiene Department said, &quot;To summarise the results of the auction for the wet goods stalls held yesterday (November 15) and today (November 16), all 175 wet goods stalls were let out, and the successful bids ranged from the opening price of $5,440 to $60,500, which averaged out to about $25,770.&quot;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The auctions for stalls of the Fa Hui Park (Sham Shui Po), Kwun Tong Recreation Ground (Kwun Tong) and Morse Park (Wong Tai Sin) LNY fairs will be held at the Assembly Hall, 2/F, Lai Chi Kok Government Offices, 19 Lai Wan Road, Lai Chi Kok, Kowloon, on November 17, 18 and 19 respectively. The auction sessions are scheduled from 9am until completion of the auction. The auction for stalls of the Cheung Sha Wan Playground (Sham Shui Po) LNY fair will be held at 2.30pm on November 19 at the above venue until completion of the auction.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The auction for stalls of Tat Tung Road Garden LNY fair in Tung Chung will be held at Rooms 1403, 1404 and 1414, Harbour Building, 38 Pier Road, Central, on November 22. The auction session is scheduled from 9.30am until completion of the auction.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The spokesman reminded the successful bidders to comply with all the stipulations and provisions as set out in the licence agreement. Otherwise, the department is entitled to terminate the agreement and the licensee shall immediately vacate the stall.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Import of poultry meat and products from Jeollanam-do Province in Korea suspended]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600534.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600534.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Centre for Food Safety (CFS) of the Food and Environmental Hygiene Department announced today (November 16) that in view of a notification from the World Organisation for Animal Health (OIE) about an outbreak of highly pathogenic H5N1 avian influenza in Jeollanam-do Province in Korea, the CFS has instructed the trade to suspend the import of poultry meat and products (including poultry eggs) from the above-mentioned area with immediate effect to protect public health in Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;A CFS spokesman said that according to the Census and Statistics Department, Hong Kong imported about 10 tonnes of frozen poultry meat and about 0.28 million poultry eggs from Korea in the first nine months of this year.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&quot;The CFS has contacted the Korean authorities over the issue and will closely monitor information issued by the OIE and the relevant authorities on the avian influenza outbreaks. Appropriate action will be taken in response to the development of the situation,&quot; the spokesman said.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[CSSA caseload for October 2021]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600303.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600303.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The overall Comprehensive Social Security Assistance (CSSA) caseload in October showed a drop of 797 cases, representing a decrease of 0.4 per cent compared with that of September, according to the latest CSSA caseload statistics released by the Social Welfare Department today (November 16).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The total CSSA caseload at the end of October stood at 218 333 (see attached table), with a total of 308 721 recipients.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Analysed by case nature, low-earnings cases registered a month-to-month decrease of 0.9 per cent to 2 251 cases. Single parent cases showed a drop of 0.8 per cent to 24 132 cases. Old age cases were down by 0.3 per cent to 124 908 cases.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Unemployment cases decreased by 1.4 per cent to 18 833 cases. The figure represented an increase of about 49.6 per cent in comparison with that of January 2020 when Hong Kong just started to fight against the COVID-19 pandemic. The average number of applications for unemployment cases in August to October 2021 was 502 per month, representing a reduction of 4.9 per cent from that in July to September.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Ill-health cases increased by 0.3 per cent to 26 781 cases. Permanent disability cases increased by 0.1 per cent to 17 527 cases.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Exchange Fund Bills tender results]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600462.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600462.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:48:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Exchange Fund Bills Tender Results:<br />
&nbsp;
<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tender date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">November 16, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Paper on offer</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">EF Bills</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue number</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">Q2146</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Maturity date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">February 16, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount applied</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">HK$106,040 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount allotted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">HK$57,170 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Average yield accepted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.07 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Highest yield accepted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.09 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Pro rata ratio*</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">About 37 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Average tender yield</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.09 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="width:561px">****************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tender date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">November 16, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Paper on offer</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">EF Bills</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue number</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">H2175</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">November 17, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Maturity date</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">May 18, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount applied</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">HK$43,650 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount allotted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">HK$17,000 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Average yield accepted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.07 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Highest yield accepted</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.08 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Pro rata ratio*</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">About 82 PCT</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Average tender yield</td>
			<td style="width:24px">:</td>
			<td style="width:253px">0.09 PCT</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;<br />
*&quot;Pro rata ratio&quot; refers to the average percentage of allotment with respect to each tender participant&#39;s tendered amount at the &quot;highest yield accepted&quot; level.<br />
---------------------------------------------------------<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hong Kong Monetary Authority Tenders to be held in the week beginning November 22, 2021:<br />
&nbsp;
<table border="0">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tender date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 23, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Paper on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">EF Bills</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue number</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">Q2147</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 24, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Maturity date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">February 23, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tenor</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">91 Days</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">HK$51,359 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="width:553px">****************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tender date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 23, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Paper on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">EF Bills</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue number</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">H2176</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 24, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Maturity date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">May 25, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tenor</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">182 Days</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">HK$15,000 MN</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td colspan="3" style="width:553px">****************************</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tender date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 23, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Paper on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">EF Bills</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue number</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">Y2197</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Issue date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 24, 2021</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Maturity date</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">November 23, 2022</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Tenor</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">364 Days</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td style="width:283px">Amount on offer</td>
			<td style="width:19px">:</td>
			<td style="width:251px">HK$5,000 MN</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
]]>			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Government strongly deplores intimidation against judicial officers]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600499.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600499.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:33:55 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In response to threatening letters received by the West Kowloon Magistrates&#39; Courts and the Shatin Magistrates&#39; Courts, the Department of Justice (DoJ) issued the following statement today (November 16):<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Intimidation against judges and judicial officers is unacceptable to Hong Kong as a society which observes the rule of law. In any event&nbsp;that unlawful means is used with an aim to exert influence over court proceedings, the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region (HKSAR) Government will take the case seriously and spare no effort in bringing the culprit to justice in order to safeguard the due administration of the judicial process and public peace.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In exercising judicial power, judges are required to handle cases strictly in accordance with the applicable law and evidence. Article 85 of the Basic Law guarantees that the courts of the HKSAR shall exercise judicial power independently, free from any interference.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The DoJ strongly deplores recent cases of criminal intimidation against judges. Offenders will be brought to justice. Under section 24 of the Crimes Ordinance, anyone who threatens any other person with injury to him/her shall be guilty and liable on conviction upon indictment to imprisonment for five years.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Unemployment and underemployment statistics for August - October 2021]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600346.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600346.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;According to the latest labour force statistics (i.e. provisional figures for August&nbsp;- October 2021) released today (November 16) by the Census and Statistics Department (C&amp;SD), the seasonally adjusted unemployment rate decreased from 4.5% in July - September 2021 to 4.3% in August - October 2021. The underemployment rate also decreased from 2.1% in July - September 2021 to 1.9% in August - October 2021.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Comparing August - October 2021 with July - September 2021, most major economic sectors saw a drop in both the unemployment rate (not seasonally adjusted) and underemployment rate. For unemployment rate, more distinct decreases were observed in the decoration, repair and maintenance for buildings sector; food and beverage service activities sector; and arts, entertainment and recreation sector. As to the underemployment rate, decreases were mainly seen in the decoration, repair and maintenance for buildings sector; and food and beverage service activities sector.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Total employment increased by around 8&nbsp;500 from 3&nbsp;658&nbsp;000 in July&nbsp;-&nbsp;September 2021 to 3&nbsp;666&nbsp;500 in August - October 2021. The labour force in August - October 2021 was 3&nbsp;838&nbsp;200, about the same as that in July - September 2021 (3&nbsp;838&nbsp;600).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The number of unemployed persons (not seasonally adjusted) decreased by around 8&nbsp;800 from 180&nbsp;600 in July - September 2021 to 171&nbsp;800 in August - October 2021. Over the same period, the number of underemployed persons also decreased by around 6&nbsp;300 from 79&nbsp;000 to 72&nbsp;700.<br />
<br />
Commentary<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Commenting on the latest unemployment figures, the Secretary for Labour and Welfare, Dr Law Chi-kwong, said, &quot;The labour market continued to improve amid the sustained economic recovery. The seasonally adjusted unemployment rate decreased by 0.2 percentage point from July - September 2021 to 4.3% in August - October 2021 and the underemployment rate also decreased by 0.2 percentage point to 1.9%. Over the same period, total employment went up by 8&nbsp;500 to 3&nbsp;666&nbsp;500, and the number of unemployed persons fell by 8&nbsp;800 to 171&nbsp;800.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Among the consumption- and tourism-related sectors, the unemployment rate of food and beverage service activities declined notably by 0.8 percentage point from the preceding three-month period to 7.7% in August - October 2021. Other sectors that showed more visible declines in the unemployment rate include the decoration, repair and maintenance for buildings sector and the arts, entertainment and recreation sector.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Looking ahead, Dr Law said, &quot;The labour market should continue to improve, but the extent of improvement would depend on the pace of economic recovery. The stable local epidemic situation and the Consumption Voucher Scheme should continue to render support to the consumption-related activities in the near term. Yet, the virtually frozen inbound tourism remains a constraint. To lay a more solid foundation for further improvement of the economy and labour market, the community should stay vigilant against the COVID-19 epidemic, strive towards more widespread vaccination and abide by the anti-epidemic measures. The Government will continue to monitor the situation closely.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;He noted that in August - October 2021, the Labour Department (LD) recorded a monthly average of 104&nbsp;915 vacancies from the private sector, representing an increase of 2.1% over the average figure in July - September 2021 and a year-on-year increase of 64.7%. Job-seekers may make use of the LD&#39;s online platforms such as the Interactive Employment Service website for obtaining such vacancy information. The LD&#39;s job centres also provide personalised employment advisory services. Employment officers will provide job-seekers with job search advice, information on the job market and training/retraining courses, and conduct career aptitude assessment, etc., in accordance with their individual needs and preferences, and match them with suitable jobs.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;On large-scale job fairs, the LD will organise the Job Fair for Middle-aged and Elderly Employment on November 25 and 26, 2021 at the MacPherson Stadium. Around 50 employers will participate, offering a large amount of job vacancies from various industries.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Further information<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The unemployment and underemployment statistics were compiled from the findings of the continuous General Household Survey.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The survey for August - October 2021 covered a sample of some 25&nbsp;000 households or 69&nbsp;000 persons, selected in accordance with a scientifically designed sampling scheme to represent the population of Hong Kong. Labour force statistics compiled from this sample represented the situation in the moving three-month period of August to October 2021.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Data on labour force characteristics were obtained from the survey by interviewing each member aged 15 or over in the sampled households.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In the survey, the definitions used in measuring unemployment and underemployment follow closely those recommended by the International Labour Organization.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Statistical tables on the latest labour force statistics can be downloaded at the website of the C&amp;SD (<a href="http://www.censtatd.gov.hk/en/EIndexbySubject.html?pcode=D5250021&amp;scode=200" target="_blank">www.censtatd.gov.hk/en/EIndexbySubject.html?pcode=D5250021&amp;scode=200</a>). More detailed analysis of the labour force characteristics is given in the &quot;Quarterly Report on General Household Survey&quot; which is published four times a year. The latest issue of the publication contains statistics for the quarter April - June 2021 while the next issue covering the quarter July - September 2021 will be available by end November 2021. Users can also download this publication at the website of the C&amp;SD (<a href="http://www.censtatd.gov.hk/en/EIndexbySubject.html?pcode=B1050001&amp;scode=200" target="_blank">www.censtatd.gov.hk/en/EIndexbySubject.html?pcode=B1050001&amp;scode=200</a>).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;For enquiries about labour force statistics, please contact the Household Statistics Analysis Section of the C&amp;SD (Tel:&nbsp;2887&nbsp;5508 or email: <a href="mailto:ghs@censtatd.gov.hk" target="_blank">ghs@censtatd.gov.hk</a>).]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Public hospitals daily update on COVID-19 cases]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600425.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600425.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hospital Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; As at 9am today (November 16), one COVID-19 confirmed patient (case number: 12343) was discharged from hospital in the last 24 hours and will continue with the 14-day post-discharge isolation.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In addition, six patients under isolation orders (case numbers: 1470, 4087, 7468, 8018, 8078 and 9907) who&nbsp;have been released earlier by the Department of Health (DH) upon recovery and are meeting the discharge criteria, have to remain hospitalised for rehabilitation or convalescence. After discussion with the DH, the Hospital Authority (HA)&nbsp;decided to categorise these patients as being discharged beginning today. In total, 12 099 patients with confirmed or probable infection have been discharged so far.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In view of the latest COVID-19 epidemic situation, all confirmed patients will be admitted to either the North Lantau Hospital Hong Kong Infection Control Centre or the HA Infectious Disease Centre at Princess Margaret Hospital starting from today for more focused manpower deployment and enhanced infection control arrangements. Currently a total of 40 confirmed patients are hospitalised in the North Lantau Hospital Hong Kong Infection Control Centre and the HA Infectious Disease Centre, and all of them are in stable condition.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The HA will maintain close contact with the Centre for Health Protection to monitor the latest developments and to inform the public and healthcare workers on the latest information in a timely manner.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[CHP investigates one additional confirmed case of COVID-19 and provides update on genome analysis of three imported cases involving local air crew and test result of environmental samples taken at Four Points by Sheraton Hong Kong Tung Chung]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600442.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600442.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Centre for Health Protection (CHP) of the Department of Health (DH) announced that as of 0.00am, November 16, the CHP was investigating one additional confirmed case of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19), taking the number of cases to 12 389 in Hong Kong so far (comprising 12 388 confirmed cases and one probable case).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The newly reported case is an imported case which involved a mutant strain. The 21-year-old female patient arrived in Hong Kong from a Group A specified place (high-risk) and tested positive during the &quot;test-and-hold&quot; arrangement upon arrival at the Temporary Specimen Collection Centre at Hong Kong International Airport.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Separately, the CHP is continuing to follow up on the three imported cases involving local cargo crew who carry the L452R mutant strain (cases 12376, 12378 and 12387). The latest whole genome sequencing analysis by the CHP further revealed that the genetic sequence of case 12387 is almost identical to that of cases 12376 and 12378. It showed that the three cases are very likely to have acquired the infection during their stay in the hotel in Germany. Follow-up actions on the cases concerned are ongoing.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Meanwhile, regarding the cluster of two cases with the Delta strain sub-lineage AY.4.2 (cases 12374 and 12382) with identical genetic sequences on the 15th floor of the North Wing of Four Points by Sheraton Hong Kong Tung Chung, the CHP collected 73 environmental samples on November 12 from the rooms concerned and common areas on the same floor. Among the 73 samples, 13 samples tested positive for SARS-CoV-2, including five samples taken inside Room 1515 (case 12374) and eight samples inside Room 1517 (case 12382). Another eight samples tested indeterminate (including three from Room 1515 and five from Room 1517). The remaining 52 samples tested negative. Disinfection in the hotel has been completed. The CHP has transferred a total of 44 guests who had stayed from November 1 to 6 on the floor concerned of the North Wing in the hotel to the Penny&#39;s Bay Quarantine Centre to undergo compulsory quarantine.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A total of 40 cases have been reported in the past 14 days (November 2 to 15) and all of them are imported cases.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The CHP&#39;s epidemiological investigations and relevant contact tracing on the confirmed cases are ongoing. For case details and contact tracing information, please see the Annex or the &quot;COVID-19 Thematic Website&quot; (<a href="https://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/index.html" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk</a>).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The spokesman for the CHP stressed, &quot;The global situation of COVID-19 infection remains severe and there is a continuous increase in the number of cases involving mutant strains that carry higher transmissibility, and there are also reports of breakthrough infections in some vaccinated individuals. The CHP strongly urges members of the public to avoid all non-essential travel outside Hong Kong, in particular to specified places with high risk under the Prevention and Control of Disease (Regulation of Cross-boundary Conveyances and Travellers) Regulation (Cap. 599H).&quot;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Cluster of parainfluenza cases at Kwai Chung Hospital]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600429.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600429.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Hospital Authority:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The spokesperson for Kwai Chung Hospital made the following announcement today (November 16):<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Three patients (aged 33 to 65) in a female psychiatric ward have presented with respiratory symptoms since November 8. Appropriate viral tests were arranged for the patients and their test results were positive&nbsp;for parainfluenza virus type 3. The patients concerned are currently under treatment with stable condition.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Admission to the ward has been suspended. Infection control measures have already been stepped up according to established guidelines. All other patients in the ward are under close surveillance.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The cases have been reported to the Hospital Authority Head Office and the Centre for Health Protection for necessary follow-up.<br />
&nbsp;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Effective Exchange Rate Index]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600215.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600215.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The effective exchange rate index for the Hong Kong dollar on Tuesday, November 16, 2021 is&nbsp;101.1 (up 0.1 against yesterday&#39;s index).]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Big-screen debut of theatre illusionist Dimitris Papaioannou's celebrated dance work (with photos)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600300.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600300.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &quot;NOWHERE&quot;, a site-specific dance piece by the celebrated Greek dance theatre director, choreographer and visual artist Dimitris Papaioannou, is making its world debut on the big screen in its director&#39;s cut this month in the New Vision Arts Festival (NVAF).<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Conceived and directed by Papaioannou, the original production &quot;NOWHERE&quot; was commissioned by the National Theatre of Greece in 2009 for the inauguration of its renovated Main Stage. The structure of the new stage became an element of the choreography. Ingeniously drawing on the new stage mechanisms, a group of humans measured the space with their bodies to confront the spatial challenges created. According to Papaioannou, &quot;NOWHERE&quot; is a series of visualised thoughts about the very nature of theatre, as a machine that mirrors human life.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Papaioannou filmed &quot;NOWHERE&quot; himself with his handheld high-definition camera. The filmed version of the central scene, dedicated to the memory of legendary choreographer Pina Bausch, who had just passed away, was released in 2014. It went viral with over 2.5 million views, and has been copied extensively. This year, the newly edited director&#39;s cut of &quot;NOWHERE&quot;, co-commissioned by the NVAF, the Dance Umbrella Festival and the Ruhrfestspiele Theatre Festival in Recklinghausen, will make its big-screen debut in Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Papaioannou, born in Athens, Greece, in 1964, gained early recognition as a painter and comics artist, before his focus shifted to the performing arts, as director, choreographer, performer, and designer of sets, costumes, makeup and lighting. He was a student of the iconic Greek painter Yannis Tsarouchis before studying at the Athens School of Fine Arts.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Papaioannou became widely known as the creator of the opening and closing ceremonies of the Athens 2004 Olympic Games. In 2017, he created &quot;The Great Tamer&quot;, his first international co-commission with 10 co-producers, including the Festival d&#39;Avignon. The production was staged in Hong Kong in 2019 and stunned the audiences.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; His latest work, &quot;Transverse Orientation&quot;, touring more than 30 cities in 2021 and 2022, will be staged at the NVAF next year.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &quot;NOWHERE&quot; (Director&#39;s Cut) is one of the programmes of the NVAF. It will be screened at 8pm on November 26 and 27 at the Theatre of Hong Kong City Hall. The programme contains nudity and audiences aged below 16 will not be admitted. There will be insightful talks by local artists after each screening.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Tickets priced at $100 are now available at URBTIX (<a href="https://ticket.urbtix.hk/internet/" target="_blank">www.urbtix.hk</a>). For credit card telephone bookings, please call 2111 5999, or use the mobile ticketing app &quot;My URBITX&quot;.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Organised by the Leisure and Cultural Services Department (LCSD), the NVAF is running from October 23 to November 28, showcasing a range of creative, pioneering and interdisciplinary programmes. For programme enquiries and concessionary schemes, please call 2370 1044 or visit <a href="http://www.nvaf.gov.hk/" target="_blank">www.nvaf.gov.hk</a>.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; All persons are required to use the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; mobile application to scan the venue QR code before they are allowed to enter LCSD offices and venues, except for exempted persons who are aged below 12 or aged 65 or above and those with disabilities that render use of the app difficult. Exemptions will also be granted to individual persons depending on the actual circumstances. All exempted persons are required to complete a record form to register their personal particulars and the date and time of their visit. As it will take time to verify personal particulars of exempted persons under the new arrangement, their waiting time for using public services or entering the relevant venues may be lengthened. The LCSD suggests that members of the public should arrive early and appeals for their understanding. The department also encourages the exempted persons to use the app as far as possible to save time.<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202503.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202503.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202504.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202504.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202505.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/16/P2021111600300_photo_1202505.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Space Museum to live stream partial lunar eclipse on November 19]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600255.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600255.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; A partial lunar eclipse will occur in Hong Kong on November 19 (Friday). This lunar eclipse follows the one that took place in May this year. Members of the public may enjoy this event during the evening when the moon rises from the east-northeast horizon. The Hong Kong Space Museum will live stream the partial lunar eclipse from 5.30pm to 7pm that day.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;At the time of moonrise at 5.38pm that day, the maximum eclipse will have already ended. The moon will be leaving the umbra gradually, at 6.47pm the moon will exit the Earth&#39;s umbra completely. The whole eclipse will end when the moon leaves the penumbra at 8.06pm. As the moon will be below the horizon at the beginning of the eclipse, part of the eclipse is not visible in Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;During the partial lunar eclipse, the moon will not be completely covered by the Earth&#39;s umbra. However, since the moon will be at a low altitude and the sky will not be completely dark when the eclipse is in progress, it may be relatively difficult for the public to clearly view the moon. The moon will still be less than five degrees above the horizon at 6pm that day. The Hong Kong Space Museum reminds the public to pay special attention to the height of obstacles in the east-northeast direction when selecting a site for observation.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Hong Kong Space Museum will live stream the partial lunar eclipse via its YouTube channel (<a href="http://www.youtube.com/hkspacem" target="_blank">www.youtube.com/hkspacem</a>). Curators will share interesting science tidbits related to lunar eclipse during the live stream. The public is also encouraged to visit the Facebook pages of the Leisure and Cultural Services Department &quot;LCSD Plusss&quot; (<a href="http://www.facebook.com/LCSDPlusss" target="_blank">www.facebook.com/LCSDPlusss</a>) and the Museum (<a href="http://www.facebook.com/hkspacem" target="_blank">www.facebook.com/hkspacem</a>) to observe the lunar eclipse in parallel.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;When the sun, the Earth and the moon are aligned, the moon will enter the Earth&#39;s shadow, resulting in a lunar eclipse. Lunar eclipses can be divided into three types, namely the penumbral eclipse, partial eclipse and total eclipse, depending on how the moon comes in contact with the Earth&#39;s umbra or penumbra. A penumbral lunar eclipse happens when the moon enters the penumbra of the Earth; whereas a partial lunar eclipse happens when only part of the moon enters the umbra. When the Earth&#39;s umbra covers the moon completely, a total lunar eclipse results. A partial lunar eclipse can be divided into five stages: moon enters penumbra, moon enters umbra, maximum eclipse, moon exits umbra and moon exits penumbra. During the partial lunar eclipse this time, only the last two stages can be seen in Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The timetable for observing the partial lunar eclipse on November 19 in Hong Kong:<br />
&nbsp;
<table border="1" style="width:500px">
	<tbody>
		<tr>
			<td>Stage</td>
			<td>Hong Kong time</td>
			<td>Moon&#39;s altitude (degrees)</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Moon enters penumbra</td>
			<td>Not visible</td>
			<td>--</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Moon enters umbra</td>
			<td>Not visible</td>
			<td>--</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Maximum eclipse</td>
			<td>Not visible</td>
			<td>--</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Moonrise</td>
			<td>5.38pm</td>
			<td>--</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Moon exits umbra</td>
			<td>6.47pm</td>
			<td>14</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Moon exits penumbra</td>
			<td>8.06pm</td>
			<td>31</td>
		</tr>
	</tbody>
</table>
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Since weather always affects astronomical observations, members of the public are advised to pay attention to the latest weather conditions during outdoor observation. The public should also comply with the latest anti-epidemic measures and maintain social distancing while staying vigilant with regards to personal hygiene. For details of the partial lunar eclipse and the live streaming, please visit the Museum&#39;s website at <a href="http://hk.space.museum">hk.space.museum</a>.&nbsp;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Government announces Study Subsidy Scheme for Designated Professions/Sectors for 2022/23 cohort - sub-degree programmes]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600195.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600195.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Government announced today (November 16) that the Study Subsidy Scheme for Designated Professions/Sectors (SSSDP) will subsidise a total of 2 501 places in 32 sub-degree programmes of eight post-secondary institutions for the cohort to be admitted in the 2022/23 academic year.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;These 32 designated sub-degree programmes fall under six disciplines that have been identified as having keen manpower demand, namely architecture and engineering, computer science, creative industries, health care, sports and recreation, and tourism and hospitality.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The sub-degree programmes and number of subsidised places under the SSSDP are determined by the Education Bureau in consultation with relevant policy bureaux and departments. Details of the participating institutions, the programmes and the number of subsidised places are listed in the Annex.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In the 2022/23 academic year, the annual subsidy amount for laboratory-based sub-degree programmes will be increased from $38,400 in the 2021/22 academic year to $38,520, while that for non-laboratory-based sub-degree programmes will be increased from $22,050 to $22,120 according to the movement of the Composite Consumer Price Index.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The adjusted subsidy amounts are applicable to both new and continuing eligible students. The subsidy is tenable for the normal duration of the programmes concerned. Students receiving the subsidy will pay a tuition fee with the subsidy applied. Students in need may still apply for student financial assistance from the Student Finance Office of the Working Family and Student Financial Assistance Agency in respect of the actual amount of tuition fee payable.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;For admission to the designated sub-degree programmes under the SSSDP, students can apply directly to the relevant institutions.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The SSSDP was launched in the 2015/16 academic year to subsidise students to pursue designated full-time locally accredited self-financing undergraduate programmes in selected disciplines with a view to nurturing talent for industries with keen human resource demand. The scope of the SSSDP was expanded with effect from the 2019/20 academic year to benefit about 2 000 students per cohort enrolling in designated full-time locally accredited self-financing sub-degree programmes in selected disciplines.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The designated undergraduate programmes under the SSSDP in the 2022/23 academic year, including the number of subsidised places and the subsidy amounts concerned, were announced on September 21.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;For details of the SSSDP, please visit <a href="http://www.cspe.edu.hk/sssdp" target="_blank">www.cspe.edu.hk/sssdp</a>.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Services of West Kowloon Magistrates' Courts and Shatin Magistrates' Courts resume]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600444.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600444.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:38:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Judiciary:&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Judiciary announced today (November 16) that the Registry and the Accounts Office of the West Kowloon Magistrates&#39; Courts, and the Registry, the Accounts Office and the Bailiff Office of the Shatin Magistrates&#39; Courts, which had been closed earlier today due to emergency incidents, have reopened at 2.30pm.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For enquiries, court users may call the General Enquiry Hotline: 2677 8373.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Partial service of West Kowloon Magistrates' Courts and Shatin Magistrates' Courts suspended]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600392.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600392.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:40:55 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[The following is issued on behalf of the Judiciary:<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Judiciary today (November 16) announced that, due to emergency incidents, the Registry and the Accounts Office of the West Kowloon Magistrates&#39; Courts, and the Registry, the Accounts Office and the Bailiff Office of the Shatin Magistrates&#39; Courts have been closed until further notice.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Court proceedings and other court business of both Magistrates&#39; Courts will not be affected.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;For enquiries, court users may call the General Enquiry Hotline: 2677 8373.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Transcript of remarks by CE at media session before ExCo (with video)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600399.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600399.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:33:41 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Following is the transcript of remarks by the Chief Executive, Mrs Carrie Lam, at a media session before the Executive Council meeting today (November 16):<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Reporter: Hello Mrs Lam. So, can I take what you just said as a denial of a news report today suggesting that there&#39;ll be a further requirement imposed on flight crew to be home quarantined for 14 days, and if that is still true, does that mean it would not apply to cargo flights&#39; pilots?<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Chief Executive: I have not read the so-called report that you referred to because I was in a function this whole morning. What I said was, as a result of a total of three cases of cargo crew being infected and confirmed upon return to Hong Kong during the regular testing, the Government, together with the airline, that is Cathay Pacific, had been in close discussion over the last few days and various enhancement measures have been imposed as a result of those discussions.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
Reporter: The Economist magazine said the Immigration Department has refused to renew the working visa of its China correspondent, Wong Sue-lin. The incident, apparently not the first of its kind in recent years, has raised concerns from the foreign press community. Will the Government be able to provide assurances to foreign journalists that their visa applications will be handled in a timely and transparent manner? And also, could you explain why the Government has decided not to renew Ms Wong&#39;s working visa? Thank you.<br />
<br />
Chief Executive: First of all, the issue of visa is the autonomy and the discretion of any government. For example, standing here as the Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, I&#39;ve been denied visa into the United States of America. Although I would dispute that, but that was the autonomy and the discretion of the US Government. It is always the discretion of the Director of Immigration to decide on the circumstances of each case whether they will grant or extend a visa, or impose certain conditions on a visa. We do not comment on individual cases. That&#39;s point number one.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Point number two is, Hong Kong is an international city, and we are very proud of being a hub for overseas media. I am sure you know that we have a large number of overseas media based in Hong Kong, some of them using Hong Kong as their regional base to operate in the Asia Pacific region. We will continue to facilitate their stay, operation and employment in Hong Kong in accordance with our policy. And of course, we now also have a piece of law called the National Security Law. In all aspects of Government activities, national security is clearly a very important consideration.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Thirdly, you asked for assurance. The assurance is provided in the Basic Law, but everything has to be done in a legitimate manner. The best way to give assurance is to look at the actual facts and figures. I understand that the Ministry of Foreign Affairs spokesman yesterday has quoted some figures. Those figures came from us. They are Immigration Department&#39;s figures on how many employment visas we have granted to overseas media over the past period, and specifically, how many of those were granted to a particular media outlet. Those are the best explanations of the Hong Kong SAR Government continuing to operate and to facilitate the operation of overseas media in Hong Kong.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
(Please also refer to the Chinese portion of the transcript.)]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Correctional officer stops remand person in custody from committing suicide by hanging]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600334.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600334.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A correctional officer stopped a 41-year-old male remand person in custody from committing suicide by hanging at Lai Chi Kok Reception Centre last night (November 15).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;At around 7.30pm yesterday, a correctional officer found the remand person in custody attempting to commit suicide by hanging with a bedsheet tied to&nbsp;a fire fighting pipe inside the laundry workshop. The officer immediately provided first aid treatment to him and called for reinforcement. The remand person in custody was found unconscious at that moment. He was sent to a public hospital for further treatment after receiving an examination and treatment by the institution medical officer. The case has been reported to the Police.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A spokesman for the Correctional Services Department said, &quot;The department uses all possible measures to prevent persons in custody from attempting suicide or self-harm. These measures include administrative arrangements, the improvement of institution facilities, staff training and first aid services.&quot;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The person in custody has been remanded for the offence of trafficking in a dangerous drug since March 2020.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Radio drama to showcase life-changing journey of trainees of Youth Employment and Training Programme]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021110300374.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021110300374.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Labour Department (LD) and Radio 2 of Radio Television Hong Kong (RTHK) will jointly present a new radio drama &quot;A Moment to Fly II&quot;, as a sequel to last year&#39;s &quot;A Moment to Fly&quot;, to promote Youth Employment and Training Programme (YETP) services. The production aims to encourage young people who might sometimes feel lost in pursuing their dreams that with courage and the persistence to try, they could all take flight on their own pathway and realise their dreams.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The radio drama consists of seven short stories adapted from the real-life experiences of some awardees of the YETP Most Improved Trainees 2020. It showcases how they have overcome various challenges in the workplace with their perseverance and passion for work, as well as with the support of their employers, case managers and family.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Featuring singers Ansonbean, Mischa Ip, Alex Fong, Shiga Lin, Aka Chio, Jace Chan and fencer Lawrence Ng, the 20-episode radio drama will be broadcast during the programme &quot;Three&#39;s a Crowd&quot; on RTHK&#39;s Radio 2 every Wednesday between 3pm and 5pm from November 17.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The YETP is open to young school leavers aged 15 to 24 with educational attainment at sub-degree level or below. Enrolment for the YETP is free of charge on a year-round basis. Services offered include pre-employment training,&nbsp;one-month workplace attachment training, on-the-job training for six to 12 months, and case management services provided by registered social workers. Trainees receive personalised career guidance, job search assistance and employment support. An off-the-job vocational training allowance and a retention allowance are provided to eligible trainees.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For details, please visit the YETP&#39;s website at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.yes.labour.gov.hk/" target="_blank">www.yes.labour.gov.hk</a>.&nbsp;The LD has also set up a Youth Employment Services hotline at 2112 9932 to provide a one-stop enquiry service regarding the programme and receive registrations of on-the-job training vacancies from employers.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Red flags hoisted at some beaches]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600241.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/16/P2021111600241.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 10:13:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[Attention TV/radio announcers:<br />
<br />
Please broadcast the following as soon as possible:<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Here is an item of interest to swimmers.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Leisure and Cultural Services Department announced today (November 16) that due to big waves, red flags have been hoisted at Stanley Main Beach and Big Wave Bay Beach in Southern District, Hong Kong Island; and Silverstrand Beach and Clear Water Bay Second Beach in Sai Kung District. Beachgoers are advised not to swim at these beaches.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Advisory Panel on COVID-19 Vaccines convenes meeting to conduct continuous benefit-risk analysis of authorised COVID-19 vaccines]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500813.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500813.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The Advisory Panel on COVID-19 Vaccines (Advisory Panel) convened a meeting today (November 15) to conduct continuous benefit-risk analysis of authorised COVID-19 vaccines. The meeting also reviewed the latest data of the two authorised vaccines immunised in different age groups and made recommendations.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The meeting today was chaired by convenor Professor Wallace Lau Chak-sing. At the meeting, on the application made by Sinovac on lowering the age limit for receiving the Sinovac vaccine to age three, the Advisory Panel reviewed the relevant information submitted by Sinovac, including the phase 1 and phase 2 clinical trial data published in peer reviewed medical journals, real-world safety data collected in Mainland China, the preliminary data from the phase 3 clinical trials conducted in countries such as South Africa and Chile, and other relevant clinical trial data. The relevant information indicated that the Sinovac vaccine had good safety when administered on children aged three to 17 of different ethnicities. Also, compared with adults aged 18 or above, children aged three to 17 developed better immunogenicity response. After considering the relevant information and weighing the risks posed by the COVID-19 epidemic to the local community, the Advisory Panel recommended to extend the eligibility of the Sinovac vaccine to cover children aged three to 17. The Advisory Panel also recommended to provide the relevant information to the Joint Scientific Committees (Scientific Committee on Vaccine Preventable Diseases and Scientific Committee on Emerging and Zoonotic Diseases) under the Department of Health for examination, in order to facilitate with determining the priority groups for receiving the relevant vaccine. The Advisory Panel will submit the above recommendation to the Secretary for Food and Health (SFH) for consideration.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Regarding the administration of the Comirnaty vaccine on children aged five to 11, the Advisory Panel noted the relevant clinical data published and the situation regarding overseas emergency use authorisation. The Advisory Panel recommended the Government to follow up with Fosun Pharma on the issue of lowering the age limit and to request Fosun Pharma to provide the relevant information.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Government spokesman said, &quot;The Government welcomes the recommendation by the Advisory Panel on lowering the age indication of the Sinovac vaccine. After examination by the Joint Scientific Committees, the SFH will consider the relevant recommendation and come to a decision as soon as possible. The Government will also follow up with Fosun Pharma on the matters related to lowering the age limit of the Comirnaty vaccine to cover children aged five to 11. The Government will continue to ensure that the authorised vaccines satisfy the criteria of safety, efficacy and quality, and will continue to disseminate the latest safety and scientific information on the relevant vaccines to the public and relevant stakeholders in a timely manner.&quot;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The SFH authorised two COVID-19 vaccines, namely the Comirnaty vaccine and the Sinovac vaccine, in accordance with the Prevention and Control of Disease (Use of Vaccines) Regulation (Cap. 599K) on January 25 and February 18 respectively. To comply with the conditions of authorisation, the authorisation applicants are required to submit the latest clinical data on the vaccines, safety update reports and quality certification documents, etc. for continuous review and monitoring.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Government gazettes compulsory testing notice]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500713.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500713.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:20:34 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;​The Government exercises the power under the Prevention and Control of Disease (Compulsory Testing for Certain Persons) Regulation (Cap. 599J) and publishes in the Gazette a compulsory testing notice, which requires any person who had been present at 19 specified premises during the specified period (persons subject to compulsory testing) to undergo a COVID-19 nucleic acid test.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In view of&nbsp;two previous imported cases who had stayed in Hong Kong during the incubation period,&nbsp;any person who had been present at four specified premises during the specified period has to undergo additional testing. &nbsp;The Government strongly reminds members of the public to strictly follow the compulsory testing requirements and undergo the multiple tests on time as required. The above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well. They are advised to closely monitor their health conditions. They should seek medical attention and undergo testing even they have only mild symptoms.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Furthermore, since there was an outbreak of upper respiratory tract infection and/or influenza-like illness in 15 schools, and the symptoms of the diseases concerned are similar to those of COVID-19, for prudence&#39;s sake, the relevant schools or their specified levels are covered in the compulsory testing notice. Persons who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course would be taken to have complied with the requirements set out in the compulsory testing notice.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Persons subject to compulsory testing in accordance with a compulsory testing notice must go to any of the mobile specimen collection stations, community testing centres (CTCs) or recognised local medical testing institutions to undergo professional swab sampling in fulfilling the requirements for compulsory testing. Young children may continue to undergo the test using a stool specimen.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;If Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 3 or above, the Red or Black Rainstorm Warning Signal or the post-super typhoon &quot;extreme conditions&quot; announcement by the Government is in force at any time during the period for undergoing the compulsory testing, the period for undergoing the compulsory testing will be further extended for one day.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Comirnaty and CoronaVac vaccines are highly effective in preventing severe cases and deaths from COVID-19. They can provide protection to those vaccinated to prevent serious complications and even death after infection. The Government appeals to persons who are not yet vaccinated, especially senior citizens, chronic patients and other immunocompromised persons who face a higher chance of death after COVID-19 infection, to get vaccinated as soon as possible for better self-protection before the fifth wave strikes in Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Details of the compulsory testing notice are in Annex 1.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Subsequent to the announcement by the Centre for Health Protection (CHP) on the updated quarantine arrangements of local COVID-19 cases with a mutant strain, persons who resided or worked within the same building as the residence of relevant cases will be subject to compulsory testing on specified dates in accordance with the announcement by the Department of Health (DH). They will also be required to undergo self-monitoring until the 21st day (see the details of the buildings and dates of testing at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/CTN_Specified_premises_and_Dates_of_Testing.pdf" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/CTN_Specified_premises_and_Dates_of_Testing.pdf</a>). For prudence&#39;s sake, the above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In accordance with the compulsory testing notice issued earlier, all household members of close contacts are required to undergo compulsory testing. Any person who had lived with a person placed under quarantine pursuant to section 22 of the Prevention and Control of Disease Regulation (Cap. 599A) (person under quarantine) in the same residential unit on the date of commencement of quarantine or during the 14 days before that day, and who becomes aware of the quarantine of the person under quarantine when the relevant quarantine has not yet been completed, has to undergo testing within two days of him or her becoming aware that the person under quarantine has been placed under quarantine and report to the Government the result of the test by phone (6275 6901), fax (2530 5872) or email (<a href="mailto:ct@csb.gov.hk" target="_blank">ct@csb.gov.hk</a>) within three days of undergoing the test. For prudence&#39;s sake, the above compulsory testing requirement applies to those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course as well.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;CTCs provide testing services for the public, including free service for persons subject to compulsory testing. Booking and walk-in services are available. Members of the public only need to provide simple personal information on the 24-hour booking system (<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en</a>). The system shows the booking status of the centres for the coming two weeks to facilitate the public&#39;s planning and selection of a suitable testing centre and a time slot for testing. The testing centres will accord priority to serve individuals with advance bookings. As of 6pm today (November 15), there were around 33 000 booking places available for tomorrow (November 16) at the CTCs, and around 93 per cent availability for booking places for the coming seven days. Members of the public may call the testing centres for enquiries on the availability of bookings or walk-in quotas before visiting the centres.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;As persons who resided or worked within the same building as the residence of local COVID-19 cases with a mutant strain will be subject to compulsory testing on specified dates in accordance with the announcement by the DH, the Government will set up mobile specimen collection stations at 15-17 Mody Road in Tsim Sha Tsui and the open-air car park, G/F, Hampton Place in Tai Kok Tsui tomorrow to provide free testing service for residents and workers of Harbour Pinnacle and Hampton Place subject to compulsory testing respectively. Outdoor mobile specimen collection stations will be closed if Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 3 or the Red Rainstorm Warning Signal is in force while all mobile specimen collection stations together with all CTCs will be closed when Tropical Cyclone Warning Signal No. 8 or higher or the Black Rainstorm Warning Signal is in force.<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Coupled with all CTCs, there will be a total of 29 CTCs/mobile specimen collection stations in various districts tomorrow to provide free service for persons subject to compulsory testing. The testing capacity should be sufficient to meet the demand. The opening dates and operating hours of the mobile specimen collection stations in various districts providing free COVID-19 nucleic acid testing services for the general public are stated in Annex 2. Persons subject to compulsory testing and those with the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; COVID-19 exposure notification or SMS notification from the CHP reminding them to undergo testing as soon as possible may receive free testing at CTCs or mobile specimen collection stations (if the service scope is applicable).<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Persons subject to compulsory testing may choose to undergo testing via the following routes:<br />
<br />
1. To visit any of the mobile specimen collection stations (see the list and target groups (if applicable) at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html</a>) for testing;<br />
2. To attend any of the CTCs (see the list at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en</a>);&nbsp;<br />
3. To self-arrange testing provided by private laboratories which are recognised by the DH and can issue SMS notifications in respect of test results (see the list at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/List_of_recognised_laboratories_RTPCR.pdf" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/pdf/List_of_recognised_laboratories_RTPCR.pdf</a>), and the relevant sample must be taken through combined nasal and throat swabs; or<br />
4. To use a specimen bottle distributed to the relevant specified premises by the CHP (if applicable), and return the specimen bottle with the stool sample collected as per relevant guidelines.<br />
&nbsp;<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;If a person subject to compulsory testing obtains a medical certificate issued by a registered medical practitioner, proving that he or she is unfit to undergo testing using a sample taken through combined nasal and throat swabs because of health reasons, then he or she may choose to undergo testing via the following routes by providing a deep throat saliva sample:<br />
1. To obtain a deep throat saliva specimen collection pack from any of the 121 post offices, vending machines set up at 20 MTR stations or 47 designated general out-patient clinics (GOPCs) of the Hospital Authority and return the specimen to one of the designated specimen collection points (see the distribution points and times, and the specimen collection points and times, at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html" target="_blank">www.coronavirus.gov.hk/eng/early-testing.html</a>);<br />
2. To undergo testing at any of the GOPCs of the Hospital Authority as instructed by a medical professional of the Hospital Authority; or<br />
3. To self-arrange testing provided by private laboratories which are recognised by the DH and can issue SMS notifications in respect of test results.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;A spokesman for the Food and Health Bureau cautioned that testing received at the Accident and Emergency Departments of the Hospital Authority or during hospital stays, or testing provided by private laboratories which cannot issue SMS notifications in respect of test results, does not comply with the requirements of the aforementioned compulsory testing notice.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;&quot;If persons subject to compulsory testing have symptoms, they should seek medical attention immediately and undergo testing as instructed by a medical professional. They should not attend the mobile specimen collection stations or the CTCs.&quot;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Persons subject to compulsory testing must keep the SMS notifications containing the result of the test and the relevant medical certificate (if applicable) for checking by a law enforcement officer when the officer requires the persons to provide information about their undergoing the specified test.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Furthermore, persons subject to testing under the compulsory testing notices should, as far as reasonably practicable, take appropriate personal disease prevention measures including wearing a mask and maintaining hand hygiene, and, unless for the purpose of undergoing the specified test, stay at their place of residence and avoid going out until the test result is ascertained as far as possible.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Any enquiries on compulsory testing arrangements may be addressed to the hotline at 6275 6901, which operates daily from 9am to 6pm. If persons subject to compulsory testing plan to conduct testing at any of the CTCs, they can check the centre&#39;s appointment status in advance. The hotlines of the CTCs are available at&nbsp;<a href="http://www.communitytest.gov.hk/en/info" target="_blank">www.communitytest.gov.hk/en/info</a>.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Government will continue to trace possibly infected persons who had been to the relevant premises, and seriously verify whether they had complied with the testing notices. Any person who fails to comply with the testing notices commits an offence and may be fined a fixed penalty of $5,000. The person would also be issued with a compulsory testing order requiring him or her to undergo testing within a specified time frame. Failure to comply with the order is an offence and the offender would be liable to a fine at level 4 ($25,000) and imprisonment for six months.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Relevant officers of different government departments are empowered to perform certain functions under the relevant Regulations under the Prevention and Control of Disease Ordinance (Cap. 599), including requesting individuals to provide information and assistance when necessary. Any person who fails to comply with the relevant request commits an offence and would be liable to a fine at level 3 ($10,000). Collection and use of any personal data for conducting COVID-19 tests must meet the requirements under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486). Government departments or testing service providers which handle the relevant information may provide the data to the DH or other relevant departments for anti-epidemic purposes as necessary. The workflow does not involve the provision of any personal data to organisations or persons outside Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The spokesman said, &quot;The Government urges all individuals who are in doubt about their own health conditions, or individuals with infection risks (such as individuals who visited places with epidemic outbreaks or contacted confirmed cases), to undergo testing promptly for early identification of infected persons.&quot;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[FEHD reminds cold store practitioners to comply with latest compulsory testing requirements on COVID-19]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500783.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500783.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;In view of the ongoing severe situation of COVID-19 infection around the world and the higher transmissibility of mutant strains which has a much faster rate of spread, the Government has strengthened the COVID-19 testing for cold store practitioners etc. under the groups of higher risks of exposure. The Food and Environmental Hygiene Department (FEHD) spokesman today (November 15) reminded cold store operators and practitioners that the Government has included designated cold store practitioners in the compulsory testing notice and the relevant persons have to undergo polymerase chain reaction-based nucleic acid test for COVID-19 regularly from November 17 (Wednesday).<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Under the compulsory testing notice to be gazetted under the Prevention and Control of Disease (Compulsory Testing for Certain Persons) Regulation (Cap 599J), cold store practitioners (including full-time, part-time, causal and relief staff, and staff under a hire-of-service contract with cold stores) who would enter the warehouse in which articles of food are stored under refrigeration inside the cold store; or come into contact with or be involved in loading / unloading of articles of food which require refrigeration, during their work or providing service, will be required to undergo testing compulsorily. Those who have completed a COVID-19 vaccination course are required to get tested once every three days, while those who have not yet completed a COVID-19 vaccination course (including staff who are unfit to receive vaccination at the moment because of health reasons) are required to get tested on a daily basis.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A spokesman for the FEHD said, &quot;To arrange more frequent regular virus testing for cold store practitioners is an anti-epidemic measure by the Government to guard against the importation of cases and the resurgence of local infections and to complement the proactive &#39;zero infection&#39; strategy. The stepped-up testing also enables staff who are exposed to higher infection risks during work to return to the community safely after work and offer protection to their families and friends in daily life.&quot;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;In addition, as the Government no longer accepts deep throat saliva specimen for compulsory or regular testing, the testing of all targeted group persons (inclusive of designated cold store practitioners), whether they have completed a vaccination course or not, must be done by using combined nasal and throat swabs collected by professionals. Also, to facilitate designated cold store practitioners included in the compulsory testing requirement, FEHD will provide additional mobile testing services for them starting from November 17. Apart from community testing centres (CTCs), eligible persons may make use of mobile specimen collection stations in various districts (such as Sha Tsui Road Playground in Tsuen Wan) and mobile specimen collection trucks set up in Sha Tin District and Kwai Tsing District to undergo testing. Relevant details will be uploaded to the FEHD webpage. Designated cold store practitioners are required to present a relevant vaccination record or medical certificate, and valid documentary proof provided by cold store operator to the staff of&nbsp;CTCs, mobile specimen collection stations or mobile specimen collection trucks for verification purpose in order to receive free testing. Furthermore, cold store operators will be required to register the number of their staff vaccinated and the relevant information online through the FEHD&#39;s webpage.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The FEHD has held a briefing session for cold store practitioners early this month to explain the latest testing arrangement, and will issue letters to cold store operators to remind them to comply with the relevant testing requirement and pay attention to take adequate personal protection measures. The FEHD has also prepared a set of Frequently Asked Questions and Answers to enable them to master the relevant information. Relevant details will be uploaded onto the FEHD webpages.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The spokesman appealed to the practitioners concerned to comply with the latest directions and arrangements to minimise the risk of COVID-19 transmission. They are also reminded to pay attention to take adequate personal protection measures at all times.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[FEHD, Customs and AFCD carried out blitz operations to combat sale of hairy crabs from dubious sources (with photo)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500698.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500698.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The Food and Environmental Hygiene Department (FEHD) continued to conduct a series of blitz operations to inspect selling points of hairy crabs in various districts and combat the illegal sale of hairy crabs, and will conduct joint operations with relevant departments if necessary to investigate the suspected sale of hairy crabs from dubious sources, with a view to ensuring that hairy crabs on sale in the market comply with regulations under relevant laws, protecting food safety and consumer rights.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;A spokesman for the FEHD said today (November 15), &quot;During the recent joint operations, the Centre for Food Safety (CFS) and the Environmental Hygiene Branch of the FEHD, Hong Kong Customs (Customs) and the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department (AFCD) detected that the source of hairy crabs sold in two retailers and their supplier which are holding Shell Fish (Hairy Crab) Permit was found to be suspicious. The premises claimed that the hairy crabs were originated from local aquaculture farm or imported from other places, but the operators failed to provide health certificate acceptable to the FEHD for inspection that breached the relevant licensing conditions. The hairy crabs claimed to be originated from local aquaculture farm were also not tagged with traceable QR code of the Accredited Fish Farm Scheme (AFFS). The FEHD has marked and sealed over 1 300 hairy crabs from the three premises. In addition, a local aquaculture farm which provided hairy crabs to the supplier was inspected during the operation. The investigation is ongoing. The department is very concerned about the sale of hairy crabs from dubious source and will continue to closely monitor the situation.&quot;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Under the Food Business Regulation (Cap. 132X) (the Regulation), save for the written permission of the Director of Food and Environmental Hygiene (DFEH), no person shall sell any restricted foods, including shell fish. Operators selling hairy crabs (including physical premises and online sale) shall obtain the Shell Fish (Hairy Crab) Permit or relevant written permission granted by the FEHD. Furthermore, the relevant regulatory condition also stipulates that hairy crabs for sale shall be obtained from a reliable and reputable source. A copy of the health certificate issued by the relevant authority and acceptable to the DFEH shall also be kept. Under the Regulation, any person who operates an unlicensed food business or sells restricted foods without permission commits an offence and is liable to a maximum fine of $50,000 and imprisonment for six months upon conviction.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In addition, according to the Public Health and Municipal Services Ordinance (Cap. 132), all food available for sale in Hong Kong, locally produced or imported, should be fit for human consumption. An offender is subject to a maximum fine of $50,000 and imprisonment for six months upon conviction. Under the Food Safety Ordinance (Cap. 612), any person who, without reasonable excuse, fails to comply with the record-keeping requirement relating to movement of food commits an offence and is liable to a maximum fine of $10,000 and imprisonment for three months upon conviction.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Customs attaches great importance to the protection of consumer rights and will take appropriate enforcement action once activities in violation of the Trade Description Ordinance (TDO) are detected in the market. The department also reminds traders not to apply a false trade description to goods or services, or to supply or offer to supply goods or services to which a false trade description is applied. Those who violate the TDO are liable on conviction to a maximum fine of $500,000 and imprisonment for five years.<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;In addition, the AFCD will monitor the culture cycle of the hairy crab farms registered under&nbsp;AFFS.&nbsp; According to the Aquaculture Manual of AFFS, before selling the hairy crabs in the registered farms, the AFCD would submit the hairy crab samples to the Government Laboratory for food safety testing and the product should pass the quality assurance prior to selling. The AFCD would issue a certificate of compliance for the batch of hairy crabs that passed the testing. Each hairy crab should also be tagged with a traceable QR code of the AFFS for identification.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The spokesman reminded the trade not to import or put on sale hairy crabs with an unknown origin, and consumers should make purchases at reputable shops with the Shell Fish (Hairy Crab) Permit or relevant written permission granted by the FEHD.&nbsp;&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;If members of the public suspect that there are operators selling hairy crabs without the relevant permits/permissions or the hairy crabs are not accompanied with health certificates, they may make a report by calling the FEHD hotline at 2868 0000 or through email (enquiries@fehd.gov.hk).<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500698_photo_1202492.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500698_photo_1202492.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Heritage Museum to feature experimental art pioneer Danny Yung's 50 years of creations (with photos)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500402.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500402.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​&quot;X-Xperimenting Exhibition - Danny Yung 50 Year Creations&quot; will be held from November 17 at the Hong Kong Heritage Museum (HKHM). Featuring cross-media works of art created by artist Danny Yung over the decades, the exhibition charts the diversified artistic journey of a forerunner of experimental art.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The opening ceremony was held today (November 15). Officiating guests included the Assistant Director (Heritage and Museums) of Leisure and Cultural Services, Ms Eve Tam; Danny Yung and his friends Mr Lau Chin-shek, Ms Anna Wu and&nbsp;Mr Tsang Tak-sing; and the Acting Museum Director of the HKHM, Dr Raymond Tang.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yung is a trailblazer in the advocacy of international cultural exchange and development. Since the 1970s, he has been keen on cross-media art creations, including film, comics, installations, video, theatre and conceptual art. In 1982, he co-founded Zuni Icosahedron, an experimental art organisation in Hong Kong, and he now serves as Zuni&#39;s Co-Artistic Director. Yung has made use of various platforms for exchanges and experimental art creations on and off the stage. For the past 50 years, he has invited artists of various media, regions and cultural backgrounds to explore the endless possibilities of cross-media creations and exchanges.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;This exhibition reconstructs and reimagines some of Yung&#39;s classic works of art. It introduces his visions and contributions in various areas, including cross-media and experimental art, visual and performing arts, art criticism, cultural exchanges, and the preservation and development of traditional craftsmanship over the years.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Highlight exhibits include &quot;Tian Tian Xiang Shang&quot;, conceptual comics that Yung started creating in the 1970s, and the &quot;Tian Tian&quot; figurines designed by people from different backgrounds whom Yung invited as part of his collaborative project. Also featured is &quot;GATEWAY - Flower Plaque Secret Garden&quot;, a large-scale flower plaque bamboo installation that combines traditional bamboo scaffolding and flower plaque crafting techniques of Hong Kong.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The exhibition is jointly presented by the Leisure and Cultural Services Department (LCSD) and Zuni, and is jointly organised by the HKHM and Zuni. Designer Freeman Lau, Zuni&#39;s Co-Artistic Director cum Executive Director Mathias Woo and Zuni&#39;s International Exchange Director, Wong Yue-wai, served as the guest curators of the exhibition. The exhibition will run from November 17 until March 14 next year at the HKHM (1 Man Lam Road, Sha Tin). For details of the exhibition and admission arrangements, please visit<br />
<a href="http://www.heritagemuseum.gov.hk/en_US/web/hm/exhibitions/data/exid270.html" target="_blank">www.heritagemuseum.gov.hk/en_US/web/hm/exhibitions/data/exid270.html</a>, or call 2180 8188 for enquiries.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;All persons are required to use the &quot;LeaveHomeSafe&quot; mobile application to scan the venue QR code before they are allowed to enter offices and venues under the LCSD, except for exempted persons who are aged below 12 or aged 65 or above and those with disabilities that render use of the app difficult. Exemptions will also be granted to individual persons depending on the actual circumstances. All exempted persons are required to complete a record form to register their personal particulars and the date and time of their visit. As it will take time to verify personal particulars of exempted persons under the new arrangement, their waiting time for using public services or entering the relevant venues may be lengthened. The LCSD suggests that members of the public arrive early, and appeals for their understanding. The department also encourages the exempted persons to use the app as far as possible to save time.<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202487.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202487.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202488.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202488.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202489.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202489.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202491.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202491.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202490.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202490.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202493.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500402_photo_1202493.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[CHP investigates outbreak of upper respiratory tract infection at kindergarten]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500692.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500692.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; The Centre for Health Protection (CHP) of the Department of Health is today (November 15) investigating an outbreak of upper respiratory tract infection (URTI) at a kindergarten in Kowloon Tong, and appeals to members of the public and staff of institutions to stay alert and maintain strict personal and environmental hygiene.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The outbreak involves 20 pupils, comprising&nbsp;10 boys and&nbsp;nine girls between 2 and 5 years old, while the details of the remaining pupil&nbsp;are pending confirmation. They developed fever, cough, runny nose and sore throat since October 23. Eighteen of them sought medical attention and&nbsp;one required hospitalisation and was discharged. All of them are in stable condition.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Officers of the CHP have advised the school to adopt necessary infection control measures against respiratory infections. The school has been put under medical surveillance. In addition, since the symptoms of URTI are similar to those of COVID-19, for prudence&#39;s sake, the school was covered in the compulsory testing notice (CTN) on October 26 to exclude the possibility of COVID-19 infection. The school has already suspended teaching activities for at least five days for cleaning and executing the CTN.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The public should maintain good personal and environmental hygiene against influenza and other respiratory illnesses and note the following:<br />
&nbsp;
<ul>
	<li>Receive seasonal influenza vaccination for personal protection;</li>
	<li>Surgical masks can prevent transmission of respiratory viruses from ill persons. It is essential for persons who are symptomatic (even if having mild symptoms) to wear a surgical mask;</li>
	<li>Wear a surgical mask when taking public transport or staying in crowded places. It is important to wear a mask properly, including performing hand hygiene before wearing and after removing a mask;</li>
	<li>Avoid touching one&#39;s eyes, mouth and nose;</li>
	<li>Wash hands with liquid soap and water properly whenever possibly contaminated;</li>
	<li>When hands are not visibly soiled, clean them with 70 to 80 per cent alcohol-based handrub;</li>
	<li>Cover the nose and mouth with tissue paper when sneezing or coughing. Dispose of soiled tissue paper properly into a lidded rubbish bin, and wash hands thoroughly afterwards;</li>
	<li>Maintain good indoor ventilation;</li>
	<li>When having respiratory symptoms, wear a surgical mask, refrain from work or attending classes at school, avoid going to crowded places and seek medical advice promptly; and</li>
	<li>Maintain a balanced diet, exercise regularly, take adequate rest, do not smoke and avoid overstress.</li>
</ul>
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Members of the public, particularly children, the elderly and those with chronic diseases, should wear a face mask and consult a doctor promptly if they develop symptoms of respiratory tract infection.]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Customs and Marine Police join forces and seize suspected smuggled goods worth about $21 million (with photos)]]></title>
			<guid>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500645.htm</guid>
			<link>https://www.info.gov.hk/gia/general/202111/15/P2021111500645.htm</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
			<description><![CDATA[&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;​Hong Kong Customs and the Marine Police mounted a joint anti-smuggling operation on November 13 and detected a suspected speedboat-related smuggling case in Tung Chung. A batch of suspected smuggled goods, including high-value food, electronic products and veterinary products, with an estimated value of about $21 million was seized.&nbsp;<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customs officers and Marine Police officers conducted a joint anti-smuggling operation at North Lantau Island during the&nbsp;small hours on that day and spotted several suspicious men loading suspected smuggled goods from a lorry to two vans in Chek Lap Kok. The two vans were subsequently driven to a seashore in Tung Chung where the goods on board were offloaded to a speedboat by several men. Customs officers and Marine Police officers then took action and the men immediately jumped into the speedboat and fled.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;During the operation, Customs officers arrested four men and detained three vehicles comprising a lorry and two vans suspected to be connected with the case. A batch of suspected smuggled goods, including dried fish maws, bird&#39;s nest, smartphones, tablet computers and veterinary products, was seized from the vehicles.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;An investigation is ongoing.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Customs stresses that it will keep up its enforcement action and will continue to fiercely combat sea smuggling activities by proactive risk-management and intelligence-based enforcement strategies, along with mounting targeted anti-smuggling operations at suitable times and maintaining close co-operation in its intelligence exchanges with local and overseas law enforcement agencies to land a solid blow against relevant activities.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Smuggling is a serious offence. Under the Import and Export Ordinance, any person found guilty of importing or exporting unmanifested cargo is liable to a maximum fine of $2 million and imprisonment for seven years.<br />
<br />
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Members of the public may report any suspected smuggling activities to Customs&#39; 24-hour hotline 2545 6182 or its dedicated crime-reporting email account (<a href="mailto:crimereport@customs.gov.hk">crimereport@customs.gov.hk</a>).<div id="photos"><a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202482.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202482.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202483.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202483.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202484.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202484.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202485.jpg" target="_blank"><img src="https://gia.info.gov.hk/general/202111/15/P2021111500645_photo_1202485.jpg" style="max-width:320px;max-height:320px" alt="Photo" border="1" /></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>